so
so
to
to
spe quick to change your
spe quick to change your
Mind And I
Mind And I
Know It's
Know It's
me follow you
me follow
I that you didn't need you want
you I that you didn't need you want
me
me
Maybe I was wrong even once wasn't
Maybe I was wrong even once wasn't
anything so If We Had another [Music
anything so If We Had another
]
[Música]
chance [
chance
tu
tu
Like You would have a
Like You would have a
[Music]
[Música]
cl How I
cl How I
was
was
about
about
[Music]
[Música]
you I Say that you didn't need what you
you I Say that you didn't need what you
want to
want to
me Maybe I was wrong even
me Maybe I was wrong even
wasn't yeah I Say that you didn't  need
wasn't yeah I Say that you didn't need
Any Part
Any Part
me yeah Maybe It's not me you should be the
me yeah Maybe It's not me you should be
one and
the one
so If We Had another chance I
e so If We Had another chance I
[Music]
[Música]
never
never
If We Had another chance I would never to [Music]
If We Had another chance I would never
my bring me Back
my bring me
If We Had another chance I would
Back If We Had another chance I would
never to Steal my [
never to Steal my
Music]
[Música]
glance bring me back to
glance bring me back to
Life
Life
I'm Broken and woken up I'm done
I'm Broken and woken up I'm done
feeling
feeling
Had I can't r your Place
Had I can't r your Place
in this
in this
G All the words you
G All the words you
speak Nothing  more to me Let over
speak Nothing more to me Let over
[Music]
[Música]
Now  And I won Let You Go I
Now And I won Let You Go I
need
need
[Music]
[Música]
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
hzm
hzm
[Music]
[Música]
from yours now I know you play
from yours now I know you play
me I Still can't
me I Still can't
believe me
believe me
on All my te the Let Start over
on All my
Now And I won't Let You Go I need to
Now And I won't Let You Go I need to
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
I'm on my own
I'm on my own
brok I feel The Rain crashing
brok I feel The Rain crashing
down all around this empty Town
down all around this empty Town
searching for the
searching for the
l But You Don't care
l But You Don't
moving like the Scars even
careware moving like the Scars even
there It's In The Air like a
there It's In The Air like a
FL
FL
[Music]
[Música]
the Give You Everything How you Close by
the Give You Everything How you Close by
the stormy se So You meant the to
the stormy se So You meant the
Kiss when you
to Kiss when you
[Music]
[Música]
for
for
you the
you the
world you give
world
You Never when I'm in Pain you
you dar You Never when I'm in Pain you
disaar like shadows
disaar like shadows
in
in
ch  the
ch the
stros I pred for you
stros I pred for you
Catch H you chas away my  fears I'm on my
Catch H you chas away my fears I'm on my
own you Made It so and Now I'm
own you Made It so and Now I'm
Chasing with the you
Chasing with
when you laugh me hope for Us Because I believe The Home you and me I thought You were the one for me That's why I give you
the you when you laugh me hope for Us
Oh I'm gna do on my
for Oh I'm gna do on my
own
own
[Music]
[Música]
no I'm do
no I'm do
this you didn't
this you did not
know I thought You were the one for me
know I thought You were the one for me
That's why I give you Everything H you Close by
That's why I give you Everything H you
the stormy seas you meant the world
Close by the stormy seas you meant the
to me [Music] musics [Music] me you
world to
got feeling
me you got
music [
music
Music] [
[Música]
Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music]
[Música]
music me
music me
Dancing
Dancing
[Music]
[Música]
music keeps
music keeps
me
me
[Music]
[Música]
on you got
on you got
feeling the
feeling the
music
music
[Music]
[Música]
musics me
musics me
Dancing
Dancing
[Music]
[Música]
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
music me
music me
[Music]
[Música]
dan music me
dan music me
dancing I get Lost inside my thoughts
dancing I get Lost inside my thoughts
and When I Start to think Oh the cls to
and When I Start to think Oh the cls to
end up on the bak I tried so hard but
end up on the bak I tried so hard but
all th Scars they Cut so Deep i b I so
all th Scars they Cut so Deep i b I so
from Heaven It's like someone clipped my
from Heaven It's like someone clipped my
Wings
Wings
Now And I can't see the ground  Can we
Now And I can't see the ground Can we
stop this
stop this
Gravity bringing me down I can't break And
Gravity bringing me down I can't bre And
I
I
[Music]
[Música]
don't
don't
[Applause] [Music] [Music]
[Aplausos]
Goodbye forg the Pain you gave me so
Goodbye forg the Pain you gave me so
long ag sleep
long
Nights I laid awake just beginning to Let go I Almost got to suicidal thoughts
ag sleep Nights I laid awake just beging
you stepped in and Angel sent from Heaven
suicidal thoughts you stepped in and
showed me how to live
Angel sent from Heaven showed me how to
Gravity it keeps bringing me down
Gravity it keeps bringing me down
I I
I I
Don't Say
Don't Say
[Music]
[Música]
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
good
good
[Music]
[Música]
[Applause] [Music] [Music]
[Aplausos]
love [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Music
love
gra
gra
[Music]
[Música]
so Why is it
so Why is it sry to Let You
so High to Let  You
so Why is it so High to Let You
[Music]
[Música]
Go
Go
so Why is it so to Let
so Why is it so to Let
[Music] [
[Música]
You
You
to Let You
to Let You
[Music]
[Música]
Go
Go
you
you
We both have thoughts of reading
We both have thoughts of
When thoughts get sm around but we
leing When thoughts get sm around but we
Keep going on
Keep going on
believing and and on all
believing and and on alled
out we don't feel like throwing it
out we don't feel like throwing it
[Music]
[Música]
all we don't feel like
all we don't feel like
but this  Time It's not about
but this Time It's not about
escaping we don't
escaping we don't
[Music]
[Música]
feel we don't feel like
feel we don't feel like
Again we don't feel like throwing it
Again we don't feel like throwing it
all we don't feel
all we don't feel
[Music]
[Música]
like
like
We both have thoughts of reading
We both have thoughts of
When thoughts get around but we
leing When thoughts get around but we
Keep going on
Keep going on
believing and on and on all
believing and on and on all
out we don't feel like it
out we don't feel like it
all we do
all
n't feel [Music] like but about
we don't feel
this Time It's not
like but this Time It's not about
escaping we don't feel like
escaping we don't feel like
[Music]
[Música]
we don't feel
we don't feel
like
like
[Music]
[Música]
don't don't
don't don't
like
like
[Music]
[Música]
took a swing at a Wrecking B And I
took a swing at a Wrecking B And I
prayed for my f I
prayed for
found a way to
myf I found a way to
reconcile In My Heart It's not
reconcile In My Heart It's not
Worth It's a Bloody Battlefield Where
Worth It's a Bloody Battlefield Where
down in the end It's all the same All
down in the end It's all the same All
You can do is play the
You can do is play the
game do is Say
game do is Say
Goodbye refuse to question s
Goodbye refuse to
to say I'm sorry
question s to say I'm sorry
so pretend that
so pretend that
Okay swear
Okay swear
[Music]
[Música]
that for One
that trying for One
Day
Day
[Music]
[Música]
these to many l to
these to many l
to
to to
[Music]
[Música]
many Leave it
many Leave it
all
all
[Music]
[Música]
kep spitting at my Feet and Force me down
kep spitting at my Feet and Force me
a Dead and Street When all I Had
down a Dead and Street When all I Had
gone Up In FL bur on
went Up In FL bur on
dark
dark
Every part of my skin I don't like the person
Every part of my skin I don't like the
within I know I'm the one to blame all I
within I know I'm the one to blame all I
can do is Take the
can do is Take the
shame do say
shame do say
good refuse to question
good refuse to question
Why I'm just to say I'm sorry
Why I'm just to say I'm sorry
so and pretend that You're Okay
so and pretend that You're
swear that You Will
Okay swear that You Will
trying for One
trying for One
[Music]
[Música]
Day [
Day
with
with
Live to many l  to
Live to many l to
many to many things
many to many things
[Music]
[Música]
to
to
al
al
[Music]
[Música]
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
Don't sick of all
Don't sick of all
these look here If I
these look here If I
size Oh [
size Oh
Music]
[Música]
no uninvited
no uninvited
home West not [Music
home West not
]
[Música]
excited my to the
excited my to the
this girl
this girl
Wonder She loves me needs to know I Love
Wonder She loves me needs to know I Love
Her I wonder If We make it through this
Her I wonder If We make it through this
sum Just W to Touch like Back When we
sum Just W to Touch like Back When we
were
were
younger
younger
yeah Why Don't You Love Me Love Me Love
yeah Why Don't You Love Me Love Me Love
meou Me
meou Me
[Music]
[Música]
tou Don't Love Me Love Me  Love Me Touch me Touch me Touch
tou Don't Love Me Love Me Love Me Touch
Me No
me Touch me Touch Me No
More Love Me Love Me love
More Love Me Love Me love
[Music]
[Música]
me me
me me
me Love Me Love Me love
me Love Me Love Me love
[Music]
[Música]
me
me
can't
can't
[Music]
[Música]
up
up
TR around
TR around
[Music]
[Música]
myup
myup
me Don't Love Me Love Me Love Me Touch me Touch
me Don't Love Me Love Me Love Me Touch
me Touch
me Touch me Touch
[Music]
[Música]
me Don't You Love Me Love Me Love Me Touch me Touch
me Don't You Love Me Love Me Love Me
me Touch Me No
Touch me Touch me Touch Me No
[Music]
[Música]
More Love  Me Love Me love
More Love Me Love Me love
me tou me tou me Touch Love Love Touch me Touch me Touch
me tou me tou me
I can't help
Touch I can't help
Myself to me I just can't get
Myself to me I just can't get
Enough I know This is love so come close
Enough I know This is love so come close
to [Music
to
] me Do
[Música]
n't Love Me Love Me Love Me T
me Don't Love Me Love Me Love Me T
T
T
love
love
Open e
Open
feel the wes Cut through me
e feel the wes Cut through me
hypnotized by the Sounds of
hypnotized by the Sounds of
B Hold
B Hold
holdem col Hold Hold
holdem col Hold
Dripping
Hold dripping
light Pain the
light Pain the
sky all Because of
sky all Because of
you tripping
you tripping
light Paint  the
light Paint the
sky only
sky only
you
you
[Music]
[Música]
make
make
Make
Make
[Music]
[Música]
Me
Me
make Last
make Last
forever stop
forever stop
in
in
surend Hold Hold
surend Hold Hold
chem Hold Hold Hold
chem Hold
dripping
Hold dripping
light Paint the sky
light Paint the sky
all Because of
all Because of
you
you
dripping Paint the
dripping Paint the
sky Only
sky Only
You can make
You can make
[Music]
[Música]
me make me make
me make
me Make
me Make
Me
Me
[Music]
[Música]
make
make
empty
empty
Heart the play with my mind got Get out
Heart the play with my mind got Get out
of
of
Tonight
Tonight
[Music]
[Música]
Run Don't Tell Myself fine
Run Don't Tell Myself fine
to just to find
to just to find
some feels
some feels
like I hate all this
like I hate all this
[Music]
[Música]
overing the more I swim the more I'm
overing the more I swim the more I'm
singing Take Me To The World of Silver
singing Take Me To The World of Silver
noak Pain Kill me somewh unf br me
noak Pain Kill me somewh unf br me
[Music]
[Música]
back
back
get me out
get me out
Now Where we
Now Where we
[Music]
[Música]
started me out of
started me out of
Now
Now
Oh me out of Broken hearts and
Oh me out of Broken hearts and
Fight
Fight
tru got get up stop wasting
tru got get up stop wasting
Time wan Run
Time wan Run
off
off
and fine to [Music]
and fine to
be just to find some the feels
be just to find some the feels
like I hate all this
like I hate all this
more I'm
overing the more I swim the more I'm
sing Take
sing Take
Me of
Me of
more Take Me some
more Take Me some
unf bring
unf bring
me
me
get me out of [
get me out of
Music]
[Música]
Now we
Now we
started out
started out
of
of
on [
on
Music]
[Música]
with My Head Again you Had Your Heart On
with My Head Again you Had Your Heart On
Me but this feels they come and go and
Me but this feels they come and go and
they come so easy Tell
they come so
me is about you That I can't forget but
me is about you That I can't forget but
Breaking Down my Walls Again just to set
Breaking Down my Walls Again just to set
me
me
free why do I baby why do I love The way
free why do I baby why do I love The way
you are Always Leave me why do I baby why do I
you are Always Leave me why do I baby
love the Touch Never Love the
why do I love the Touch Never Love the
feeling why do I baby why do  I love The
feeling why do I baby why do I love The
way you are Always Leave me why do I
way you are Always Leave me why do I
baby why do I love the T the [
baby why do I love the T the
Music]
[Música]
feeling
feeling
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
Stay up When I go out you got know all
Stay up When I go out you got know all
yours but When I say What about
yours but When I say What that about
you your
you your
words Tell me why you have to seem so
words Tell me why you have to seem so
when I'm Hold You your fingertips are
when I'm Hold You your fingertips are d
away And Love How it
away And Love How it
hurts why do I baby why do I love The way
hurts why do I baby why do I love The
you are Always Leave me why do I baby why do I
way you are Always Leave me why do I
love the tou Never  love
baby why do I love the tou Never love
theing do I baby why do I love The  way
theing do I baby why do I love The way
you are Always Leave me why do I baby why do I love the t
you are Always Leave me why do I baby
Never Love the
why do I love the t Never Love the
feeling why do I baby why do I why do I baby why do I why do I B why do I love The Love
feeling why do I baby why do I why do I
[Music]
[Música]
ha
ha
Riders
Riders
right they
right they
know
know
Li they W to
Li they W to
show
show
singers sing what they
singers sing what they
told but I know you got something Else
told but I know you got something Else
to
to
say langage [
say langage
Music] Speak I do
[Música]
n't know You are you are you are you
Speak I don't know You are you are you
are over my heart Dan Over The Dark I don't I don't I don't
are over my heart Dan Over The Dark I
know Who You are you are you are
don't I don't I don't know Who You are
you are Let sprink All
you are you are you are Let sprink All
Over If I the It makes me na
Over If I the It makes me
I
na I
like
like
got
got
[Music]
[Música]
with
with
adct
adct
to
to
cer in the
cer in the
Li
Li
show a  real good
show a real good
Time Oh I know you got something Else
Time Oh I know you got something Else
for
for
me
me
Secret language speaking in t sn you TR I
Secret langage speaking in t sn you TR I
don't know what you are you are you are you are over
don't know what you are you are you are
my heart wh dancing Over The
are over my heart wh dancing Over The
Dark I don't I don't I don't know You are you are you are you are
Dark I don't I don't I don't know You
Let over Body
are you are you are you are Let over
If [Music
If
]
[Música]
mak no Touch and Sign I like should
mak no Touch and Sign I like should
Run me exit With
Run me exit With
[Music]
[Música]
Your
Your
Touch oh
Touch oh
[Music]
[Música]
oh my heart
oh my heart
It's my body's breathing It's  just
It's my body's breathing It's just
[Music]
[Música]
you and
you and
me my heart It's be
me my heart It's
my body's breathing It's just
be my body's breathing It's just
you and
you and
[Music] me
[Música]
so c this was so l Deep
me so c this was so l Deep
can't forever the one you call let's th
can't forever the one you call let's th
so c in this was so Lost Deep it Can't
so c in this was so Lost Deep it Can't
Stop I'm forever the you
Stop I'm forever the
let's three [Music
you let's
] Let Let let
[Música]
so In
so
My Heart
In My Heart
It's my body's breathing It's just [
It's my body's breathing It's just
Music]
[Música]
you my
you my
heart My Body breathing It's just
heart My Body breathing It's just
[Music]
[Música]
you so
you
was so Lost Deep  in it Can't Stop I'm
so was so Lost Deep in it Can't Stop I'm
forever
forever
you
you
let's so
let's
we so l Deep ca
so we so l Deep
n't the you call [Music
can't the you call
let
let
so [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [
so
B
B
stranded in the
stranded in the
Open ded out Tears of
Open ded out Tears of
sorrow laing all
sorrow laing all
emotion
emotion
staring down the barrel waiting for The
staring down the barrel waiting for The
Final Gates to
Final Gates to
Open to a New
Open to a New
tomorrow moving with
tomorrow moving with
the
the
following the light that
following the light
me
me
[Music]
[Música]
Oh
Oh
hour one hour okay not of great
una horita una horita está bien no de
music not one hour of great music
musicón no una horita de musicote
damn your new
[__] tu nuevo canal de
music channel It was about time
música Ya era hora
Shameless well let's
Sinvergüenza bueno
see Ha watching H no no no no I wasn't
ver Ja viendo H no no no no estaba
watching HB it's that I was at McDonald's I
viendo HB es que estaba en el McDonald's
went to dinner let's go to the car in
he ido a cenar vamos he ido al má auto a
a moment to buy myself something But there were a
un momento a comprarme algo Pero había
lot of people hx Thank you very much
mucha gente hx Muchísimas gracias
welcome well let's see I'm going to check
bienvenido bueno a ver voy a comprobar
First of all if the members thing is
Antes que nada si lo de los miembros es
real we don't forgive you grandpa one in the
real no te perdonamos abuelo una de la
morning of music let's do let's
mañana de música vamos a
see leave me a
a ver dejarme un
moment dude it's that I had to
momento buah tío es que tenía que
eat it's that I had to eat what
comer es que tenía que comer qué
explanation do you have for this nothing
explicación tiene sobre esto nada
none life let's see
ninguna la vida a ver
members
miembros
1943 Come on today they have gone up a little eh
1943 Venga hoy han subido un poco eh
1943 eh today they have gone up eh
1943 eh hoy han subido eh
1943 there the truth is that it is
1943 ahí la verdad es que es
the truth is that it is to
la verdad es que es para
defame well there are no worse things
funarte bueno tampoco hay cosas peores
eh There are worse things in
eh Hay cosas peores en la
[Music]
[Música]
life you have no shame old ex bald I will
vida no tienes vergüenza viejo ex calvo
not contradict you The
no te llevo la contraria La
truth is I cannot refute
verdad no puedo rebatir
that but what's wrong
eso pero y que pasa
something have you given have you given chat that I have been
algo habéis dado habéis dado chat que he
out you have given super chat while I have been out
fuera habéis dado super chat mientras
or what Or you have not
que he estado fuera o qué O
given super chat while I have been
tampoco habéis dado super chat mientras
out or what let's see I'm going to
que estado fuera o tampoco a ver voy a
see no yes yes no no no you have not given
verlo no sí sí no no no no habéis dado
super chat an hour here working for
super chat una hora aquí trabajando
free an hour here working for
gratis una hora aquí trabajando
free But what is
gratis Pero qué es
this at least you are sincere Well of course Let's
esto al menos eres sincero Bueno claro A
see why I am going to lie I lied
ver por qué voy a mentir mentí las
lies have very
mentiras tienen las patas muy
short legs but listen to me let's see Oh how I have
cortas pero escúchame a ver Oh cómo me
been after eating I don't know if I feel like
he quedado después de comer yo no sé si
making salt now Oh how I have
tengo ganas de hacer sal ahora Oh cómo
been  man i did a
me he quedado tío he hecho un directo de
4 and a half hour live between gossip [ __ ] i
4 horas y media entre
just did an hour of
salseo [__] acabo de hacer una hora de
live an hour of live you didn't
directo una hora de directo no habéis
give super chat but this is a [ __ ]
dado super chat pero esto es una [__]
mess we're not going
ruina así no vamos a ninguna
anywhere like this a [ __ ] hour of live and without
parte una [__] hora de directo y sin
super chat let's see i'm going to put this Only
super chat a ver voy a poner esto Solo
for
para
subscribers i'm going to put this monetized
suscriptores voy a poner esto monetizado
that comes out in an ad man [ __ ] how
que salga en anuncio cha tío [__] qué
stiff dude what a [ __ ] [ __ ]
tiesos tío de [__] [__]
Hey [ __ ] how stiff
Eh [__] qué tiesos
[ __ ] come on
cabrones venga
lur Thank you very much welcome see it
va lur Muchas gracias bienvenido lo ve
urbin becomes a member little by little Hey
urbin se hace miembro poco a poco Oye
but at least today we reached
pero qué menos que hoy llegásemos a los
2000 members no I think I've
2000 miembros no yo creo que me lo he
worked hard And he still has the nerve to say that
currado Y todavía tiene la cara de decir
XD for those who want to strike
eso XD para los que quieren hacer huelga
put the crab in the let's see crab
pongan el cangrejo en el a ver cangrejo
in the chat if you want to strike come on and I'll
en el chat si queréis huelga venga va y
get here the fall of jabi
me pongo yo aquí la caída de jabi
oliveira like that he lost everything he's a
oliveira así lo perdió todo es un
shameless man he ID I went to
Sinvergüenza [__] macho he ID he ido a
eat I went to eat at the same time that
comer he ido a comer a la vez que sa
the dog ends man I went to eat at the same
acaba el perro tío he ido a comer a la
time that the dog ends man the dog
vez que se acaba el perro tío el perro
also wanted  go out to
también quería salir a
see capricious
ver caprichoso
note person occurs to him or her I mean
nota persona se le ocurre o sea sea
literally I opened Stream and
literalmente he abierto Stream y me he
went to the ma car Yes yes I am yes I am
ido al ma auto Sí sí soy sí soy
went to the macauto
ido al macauto
yes I am I am and there were a lot of people going very
sí soy soy y había mucha gente iba muy
slow eh I don't know what was happening today but I was going
lento eh No sé qué pasaba hoy pero iba
very slow it took them a long time
muy lento han tardado
welcome Luis Triana welcome Hey
bienvenido Luis Triana bienvenido Oye
but I see that today let's see report all
pero yo veo que hoy a ver reportar todos
the
los
Spaniards activate
españoles activemos
xenophobia report remember to be humble
xenofobia reportar recuerda ser humilde
Javi [ __ ] Here you are also going to make me
Javi [__] Aquí también me vais a hacer
be humble and look good here with the
ser humilde y quedar bien aquí con los
kids I have confidence I don't have to
chavales tengo confianza no tengo que
act like with the ladies no that I have to
hacer papel como con las señoras no que
put on a good boy plan let's see
me tengo que poner plan niño bueno a ver
the Spaniards report 20 members
repórtense los españoles 20 miembros
today the debate is strong and the pulse is like this
hoy el debate fuerte y el pulso es así
eh I mean in that plan we can't lower
eh o sea en ese plan no podemos rebajar
ourselves we can't mess around with nonsense
noos no podemos andarnos con tonterías
okay Spaniards give away 20 members each
vale españoles regalan 20 miembros cada
Latin Americans 10 damn but it is like that
latinoamericanos 10 ostia pero es así
but that has been very funable No that has
pero eso ha sido muy funable No eso ha
been super funable let's see the reality
sido super funable a ver la realidad
abusive crab a kiss alegui Thank you very much let's
cangrejo abusivo un beso alegui Muchas
see that has been that has been the
gracias a ver eso ha sido eso ha sido la
reality eh There  that assume it no don't
realidad eh Hay que asumirlo no no me
come to me now with don't come to me Now
vengáis ahora con no me vengáis Ahora
as if you were made of
como si fuerais de
glass don't come to me Now as if
cristal no me vengáis Ahora como si
you were made of glass okay with the
fuerais de cristal vale con las
nonsense no no Viva Mxico no Mxico 10
tonterías no no Viva México no México 10
Latin American members 10
miembros latinoamericanos 10 miembros
Spanish members 20 That is the plan to reach
españoles 20 Ese es el plan para llegar
3000 members the
a los 3000 miembros la
elite Saro a
élite Saro un
kiss it's very expensive I don't care I don't care
beso es muy caro me la pela me la pela
your life Jos Luis for that you
tu vida José Luis para eso
work very well this welcome
trabajas muy bien sto bienvenido
welcome but it's that I don't even know where
bienvenido pero es que no sé ni de dónde
you're from des
eres del des
true let's get to it okay I have a lot of work let's get to it I
cierto vamos al lío vale que tengo mucho
have a lot of
trabajo vamos al lío que tengo mucho
work let's concentrate in the
trabajo vamos a concentrarnos en el
living room cocu spoke today he spoke
salito ha hablado hoy cocu ha hablado
again today alegi Thank you very much for
hoy otra vez alegi Muchas gracias por
becoming a member Thank you very much friend
hacerte miembro Muchas gracias amigo
Thank you to all of you who are becoming members
Gracias a todos los que os estáis
okay I said it today we have
haciendo miembro vale lo he dicho hoy
a big fight here eh
tenemos un pulso aquí gordo que hacer eh
today we have a big fight here I
hoy tenemos aquí un pulso gordo que
trust you scoundrels
hacer Confío en ustedes sinvergüenzas
Okay let's see listen to me cocu today he
Bueno a ver escúchame cocu hoy ha vuelto
spoke again after yesterday and why he
a hablar después de lo de ayer y por qué
spoke again because he says that both
ha vuelto a hablar porque dice que tanto
Nicki Nicole and  la
Nicki Nicole como la
juaki lurbin Thank you very much but
juaki lurbin Muchas gracias pero la
next time Give me more money so
próxima vez Dame más dinero para que
your message sounds Okay Luca one How are you going to
suene tu mensaje Vale Luca uno Cómo va a
give one away
regalar uno
Bastard how are you going to give one away that you
Cabrón cómo va a regalar uno que me
're throwing in my face a member take
estás tirando a la cara un miembro toma
but let's see I feel hast humiliated
pero a ver Me siento hast humillado
Lucas I would thank you yes if there were
Lucas te daría las gracias si si fueran
10 but it's that with one what do I
10 pero es que con uno qué
do curious Thank you very much for
hago curioso Muchísimas gracias por
renewing let's see
renomar a ver
listen to me the cocu
escuchadme el cocu
hesitating the ccu
vacilando el ccu
hesitating and acting tough acting
vacilando y haciéndose el Duro
tough that they haven't picked up
haciéndose el Duro que no les ha cogido
the phone that Niki Nicole and juaki
el teléfono que Niki Nicole y la juaki
haven't stopped calling him but now
no han parado de llamarle pero que ahora
he's decided to
él ha decidido
ignore them what do you
ignorarlas qué os
think what do you think about the ccu
parece qué os parece el ccu
come on
vamos
super proud eh also he says Yes yes they
super orgulloso eh además dice Sí sí se
thought they were above me Well let's
creían por encima de mí Bueno vamos a
see better not this This is divine eh
verlo mejor no esto Esto está divino eh
the only thing I can tell you that I
lo único que les puedo decir que me
really want mda news to
mucho que quiero que mda noticias lo
upload it calmly is that lai spoke to me
suba tranquilo es que me habló lai me
Nick Nicole spoke to me really angry both of them
habló Nick Nicole re enojad las dos
indignant but of course when I speak to them
indignadas pero claro cuando les hablo
I don't even read you now they want to speak
yo ni te leen ahora quieren hablar
clearly what I do
claramente lo que hce
fen
fen
suo
suo
The  stingy Don
El avaro Don
canjo what a guy really if you're going to
canjo que tío de verdad si vais a
write if you're going
escribir si vais
to if you're going to stop my live stream so
a si vais a pararme el directo para que
I can listen to you oliveira the humble
yo os escuche oliveira el humilde
Thank you lampur see it that's very
Gracias lampur lo ve tú eso si está muy
good 500 bits Thank you very much lampur if you're
bien 500 bits Muchas gracias lampur si
going to stop the live stream so I can
vais a parar el directo para que os
listen to you okay if you're going to make me stop the
escuche vale si me vais a hacer parar el
live stream if you're going to make me stop my
directo si me vais a hacer parar mi
content creation okay if you're going to make me stop my
creación de contenido vale si me vais a
content creation
hacer parar mi creación de contenido
and you're going to contaminate my
y Vais a contaminar mi
Stream
Stream
my
mi
entertainment my art if you're going to
entretenimiento mi arte si vais a
interrupt my
interrumpir mi
art Learn to write please make it
arte Aprender a escribir por favor que
understood what the robot says
se entienda lo que dice el robot
that [ __ ] [ __ ] said that
ese [__] [__] dicho ese
kid ignore them and I sent them to the
chaval ignorarlas y las mandé a la
others folder where I'm not going to read the
carpeta otros donde no voy a leer los
messages they send me because of course
mensajes que me envíen porque claro
when one wants to talk no ah but
cuando uno quiere hablar no ah pero para
when They want to talk you have to
cuando Ellas quieren hablar hay que hay
hold the candle make them
que hay que sostenerle la vela hacerles
some mate and let them talk that's it the v the
un matecito y que hablen ya está la v la
pig Man that's it but but but well
puerca Man ya está pero pero pero bueno
this is ivay What have you done uncle IV
es que esto ivay Qué has hecho tío IV
this is your fault eh or so I consider
esto es culpa tuya eh o sea yo Considero
that this is  Ivai's fault literally or
que esto es culpa de ivai literalmente o
rather he has put it through the
sea lo ha puesto por las
roof he has put it through the roof the guy is
nubes lo ha puesto por las nubes el tío
now talking to Nicki Nicole and
ahora le habla Nicki Nicole y le habla
the other one is talking to him and now he doesn't want to talk and he
la otra y ahora no quiere hablar y las
has put them in the ignore folder to
ha pasado a la carpeta de ignorar para
never read them ever
no leerlas nunca
again mother of beautiful love and mother of
jamás madre del amor hermoso y madre del
beautiful love and wanted to talk I
amor hermoso y quería hablar Yo siempre
was always me always wanted I always wanted to
fui yo siempre quería Siempre quise
talk I always went for
hablar siempre fui por el lado del
dialogue let that be clear and I said it and I
diálogo eso que quede claro y lo dije y
will continue saying it and defending
lo voy a seguir deciendo y defendiendo
dialogue is the most precious thing there is
el diálogo es lo más preciado que hay
when dialogue doesn't exist
cuando no existe el diálogo se pierde
everything is lost the capacity of the possibility that we have to
todo la capacidad de la la posibilidad
dialogue is
que tenemos de dialogar es
super important but we all dialogue it's not
superimportante pero dialogamos todos no
just you telling me what you think and then you
solo me decí vos lo que pensás y después
ignore me now the one who is ignoring is me And
me ignoras ahora el que ignora soy yo Y
look how things are literally
fíjate Cómo están las cosas literal
missed call missed call
llamada perdida llamada perdida llamada
missed call I'm not going to answer I don't give anything
perdida No voy a atender no le deo nada
to anyone That's it you didn't want to talk done I
a nadie Ya está no querías hablar listo
spoke to my Stream I already downloaded I
hablé con mi Stream ya me descargué No
have nothing else to talk to anyone but you
tengo más nada que hablar con nadie pero
're doing what you don't like to be
estás haciendo lo que no te gusta que te
done to you Obviously obviously what do you think that I
hagan Obvio obvio qué te pensas que
want to make peace now it's too
quiero hacer las pases ahora ya es muy
late Man already  the tab jumped what do I
tarde Man ya saltó la ficha para qué
want it for? Also, it's worth it to them,
quiero también ya les vale
eh, it's worth it to start calling
eh también ya les vale ponerse a llamar
the CCU because because I said I don't know
al ccu porque porque haya dicho no sé
what on live television, what do you care, what do you
qué en un directo qué más les
care? The only one I would talk to is Mara borra, literally, the only one, the only one I would talk to is Mara Becerra, you have to prove that you're more and answer her, no, no, because if I wanted to talk, I would answer her but I don't want to talk, I don't want to talk anymore, it
pero yo no quiero hablar ya no quiero
's late, I had to smoke it in a pipe, dude, and they think that now I'm going to go with the tired horse. Ah, no, stop, let's talk, these things can be fixed, no, I'm also telling you, eh, you don't have to give people back how they behave with you, okay, I don't know, in this case, the
contigo vale No sé en este caso la
story that you've had is more than what
historia que han tenido más que lo que
we heard yesterday, I don't really know if in
escuchamos ayer no sé realmente si si en
this CCU it really helped you a lot, I don't know if
esta czu sí que les ayudó mucho No sé si
mm cocu deserved that you ignore it or if
mm cocu se merecía que lo ignoras o las
other people have come up, okay, But
otras gentes han venido arriba vale Pero
also one thing that I always keep in
igualmente una cosa que yo siempre tengo
mind, Javi says hello, IB, who is
presente Javi saluda IB que está
online and there's an exclusive, this month it
conectado y va una exclusiv este mes
has to fall, not again, not another
tiene que caer no otra vez no otra
exclusive.  no, things are
exclusiv no que está la cosa esta semana
very quiet this week eh I'm having to
muy tranqui eh estoy teniendo yo que
take pictures with Jorge Javier so that
hacerme fotos con Jorge Javier para que
people have content yesterday I found
la gente tenga contenido ayer encontré
a video of cocu where he made his
un vídeo de cocu donde hacía llorar a su
ex cry live yes yes yes yes yes there are many
ex en directo sí sí sí sí sí hay muchos
videos like that but oh well eh No, I don't think he's
vídeos así pero bueno eh No no me parece
the worst Alba a kiss Thank you Alba
el peor Alba un beso Gracias Alba
very beautiful
guapísima
e You don't have to be or return what has been
e No tienes por qué tú ser o devolver lo
done to you always 100% you
que te han hecho siempre al 100% tú
can sometimes prove that you are
puedes en algunas ocasiones demostrar
better okay Yes it's true that I
ser mejor vale Sí que es verdad que
also tell you one thing
también te digo una cosa
eh You don't give anyone what that someone would
eh No le deja a nadie lo que ese alguien
n't do for you okay I mean That's how it is That's
no haría por ti vale o sea Eso es así
something that I have learned already and I
Eso es una cosa que he aprendido yo ya y
have it completely implemented ima
la tengo completamente implementadas ima
in my life Well for me it's not like that they
en mi vida Bueno para mí no es así
have a tremendous ego nobody came to me to
tienen un ego tremendo ninguna me vino a
say Hey the truth is I was wrong I jumped to the
decir Che la verdad me equivoqué saqué
wrong conclusion nobody came to me to
una conclusión errada ninguna me vino a
tell me that, that Leo do you understand nobody
decir eso ese Leo entendés ninguna me
told me Hey the truth eh misinterpreted what
dijo Che la verdad eh malinterpretó lo
you said it wasn't that bad I think I
que dijiste no era para tanto creo que
exaggerated and I stopped following you right away
sobre exager y te dejé de seguir de de
as if I don't know as if we couldn't
una como si no sé como si no pudiéramos
talk about it before nobody came to me to say
hablarlo antes ninguna me vino a decir
that too  you should be a better
eso igual vos tendrías que ser mejor
person and send him a message saying
persona y mandarle un mensaje diciendo
listen to me I wanted to solve it but you didn't
escuchame quise solucionar y no me
answer me now it's too late I'm
respondiste ahora ya es tarde me
venting to my people and I'm the bad guy that's implied I don't have to
descargo con mi gente y soy el malo eso
send a
está implícito no tengo que mandarle un
message explaining that to anyone because
mensaje explicándole eso a nadie porque
that's implied it's understood I did this
eso está implícito se entiende hice esto
because you didn't answer me I already
porque vos no me respondiste yo ya lo
said it it's already known why I did what I did I
dije ya se sabe por qué hice lo que hice
did what I did As a consequence of
hice lo que hice En consecuencia de
trying to talk things out trying to
intentar dialogar las cosas de intentar
fix things and And mind you I don't
arreglar las cosas y Y ojo yo no las
try to fix them out of ego of saying everything
intento arreglar des ego de decir todo
well you are wrong no
bien ustedes están equivocados no las
cos a kiss Joel saying ok I
cos un beso Joel diciendo ok pido
apologize for this If it bothered you
disculpas por esto Si te
Do it buddy man Thank you very much Luis
Hazlo colega tío Muchas gracias Luis
Triana Do it and you can IV could be
Triana Hazlo y tú puedes IV podría ser
the new idol of gossip
el nuevo ídolo del salseo
man it could be m exclusive if you wanted I ask for your
tío podría ser m exclusiva si quisieras
forgiveness understand going down going down
te pido perdón entend bajando bajando
always going down the subject It's that I only go
siempre bajando el tema Es que yo solo
down and that gives me a lot of laziness always the one
bajo y eso me da mucha paja siempre el
who lets his guard down is one the other
que baja la guardia es uno las otras
people and and we all know why
personas y y todos sabemos por qué es
that is because they feel much more they feel
eso pues se sienten mucho más se sienten
much more I'm going to support Mara no matter what
mucho más yo a María la voy a bancar
happens she is the only one  that she
pase lo que pase es es la única que me
unfollowed me and I said I suck a I
dejó de seguir y dije me chupo un me
suck an egg I'm going to keep
chupo un huevo Yo la voy a seguir
following her the others like
siguiendo las otras como
why I mean Maria Becerra Why
que por qué O sea María Becerra Por qué
with Maria if she crawls be it Maria
con María si se si se arrastra sea María
Becerra unfollows him and he doesn't
Becerra lo deja de seguir a él y él no
unfollow her
le quita el
Why Why And why
follow Por qué Por qué Y por qué a ella
if she wants to respond to him I mean look at you Maria
si le quiere responder o sea fíjate tú
Becerra unfollows him
que María Becerra lo deja de seguir
Maria Becerra unfollows him and he doesn't unfollow him and
María Becerra lo deja de seguir y él no
yet Maria Becerra isn't
le quita el follow y sin embargo María
calling him nor is she going to
Becerra no lo está llamando ni lo va a
call him I don't think it looks like she's going to call him
llamar yo creo que no tiene pinta de que
and she says hey the
lo vaya a llamar y dice é yo con la
only one I would talk to would be Maria
única que hablaría sería con María
Becerra Why do you think that change is
Becerra Por qué creéis que es ese cambio
ROM
ROM
member Roman a
miembro Román un
member But what's going on What are we at, we're
miembro Pero y qué pasa A qué estamos
18 you've already spent everything you've
estamos a 18 os habéis gastado ya todo
been on other channels or what do you
habéis estado en otros canales o qué
have to always leave everything here
tenéis que dejarlo siempre todo aquí
eh a
eh un
member But what do we do with a member
miembro Pero qué hacemos con un miembro
with that let's go not even the french fry from the
con eso vamos ni la patata frita del
menu that I just ate I forgive you
menú que me acabo de comer te perdono
for everything n
por todo n
and it churra that you well that  enjoy
y it churra que tú bien que disfrut aquí
the gossip here eh pay for the gossip and
del salseo eh paga por el salseo y
go with a band personally and I'm going to
va una banda en lo personal y voy a
follow people who are a recipe it's not much
seguir a gente que es receta no es mucho
what I ask for I don't ask for anyone to
lo que pido yo yo no pido que nadie me
suck my ass I don't ask for anyone to
chupe el culo Yo no pido que nadie me
tell me anything if they want not to talk to me
diga nada si quieren que no me hablen
But the only thing I ask is that if you're
Pero yo lo único que pido es que si te
going to get mad at least talk to me Before you
vas a enojar mínimo hables conmigo Antes
understand ask me I feel that
entendés me preguntes siento que es muy
what I'm asking is very basic I understand that
básico lo que estoy pidiendo Yo entiendo
there are people who know that I need or
que hay gente que sab que yo necesito o
expect them to talk to me all the time or to be on
pretendo que me hablen todo el tiempo o
top of me or to thank me for
que me estén encima o que me agradezcan
something
algo
alexos this now now is going to be the
alexos esto ahora ahora va a ser la
grace of the day I mean the grace of the day is going to be
gracia del día o sea la gracia del día
giving away a
va a ser regalar un
member you have taken it as the joke
miembro lo habéis cogido como el chiste
of the day don't come on Haha you can put
del día no venga Jaja podéis poner todo
everyone Haha in the chat please come on
el mundo Jaja en el chat porfa venga
you can you can put everyone in
podéis podéis ponerlo todo el mundo en
the chat stop stop look look Angel
el chat para para mira mira Angel
has also given one away Haha Ha ha
también la ha regalado uno
haaja Look at one
jaaja Mira uno
Hahaha
Jajaja
haaja How
jaaja Qué
funny super
divertido super
funny
gracioso ya
we have laughed enough
nos hemos reído
we have laughed
suficiente nos hemos reído lo
enough come on okay come on okay  We
suficiente venga vale venga vale
continue, okay guys, your thing is very fun.
seguimos vale chicos muy divertido lo
I don't want anyone to
vuestro yo no quiero que nadie me
thank me for anything. It's about the fact that we
agradezca nada se trata de que nos
all know each other. We all know who's who
conocemos todos todos sabemos Quién es
and we all know what each
quién y todos sabemos lo que hizo cada
one did and yet we turn a deaf ear to each
uno y aún así hacemos oído sordo entre
other. That's not enough because there are people that
nosotros eso no da porque hay gente con
I'm not interested in talking to. They have already shown their true
la que no me interesa hablar ya mostró
colors and don't represent me. I thought at
la lacha y no me representa Pensé en
some point that they represented me. I thought
algún momento que me representaba Pensé
at some point that it was worth it.
en algún momento que valía la pena hoy
Today they don't
en día no me
represent me, why am I going to talk? In fact, they
representan para qué voy a hablar es más
gave me a quota of, like they
me dio una cuota de de de como que me
gave me a feeling of, Okay, it's your turn
dio una sensación de Okay es tu turno
now, no, I'm not going to send it. There's something that
ahora no no la voy a mandar hay algo que
roots me, Maria, in a special way.
me arraiga María de una forma especial
I have an internal band that I don't
Yo tengo una banda internas que no
think I'm going to say because I'm
pienso decir porque ya cosas personales
not going to bring out personal things, you understand, like internal things
no voy a sacar entendés como de internas
in the scene and things like that. Clearly,
de la escena y cosas así claramente no
I'm not the only one that these things happen to.
soy el único que le pasan estas cosas
But well, maybe I'm the only one who
Pero bueno quizás soy el único que se
dares to talk to us, but I'm not the only one that
anima a hablarnos pero no soy el único
happens to me, I mean, the only thing I'm going to
que le pasa o sea lo único que voy a
say about that is that I literally
decir con respecto a eso es que literal
finished the Stream. You saw the video.
terminé los el Stream vieron el video
Mega Javi says, thanks the members,
dice el Mega Javi agradece los miembros
but ccuno responds to them out of ego XD but
pero ccuno les responde por ego XD pero
Gino I understand  that when he has
Gino Yo entiendo que esto cuando lo ha
done this it is because he will feel
hecho es porque se sentirá
for I understand that when he is
por Yo entiendo que cuando esto lo está
doing this it is because he feels
haciendo es porque porque se siente
supported Not because today he will have felt
apoyado No porque hoy se habrá sentido
supported and
arropado y
Jai is humble he thanks the members I
Jai se humilde agradece los miembros
thank these members one by one the
agradezco a estos miembros uno a uno los
members But hello hello hello gifted a
miembros Pero hola hola hola regalado un
member But what is the next thing I have to be
miembro Pero qué es lo próximo que tengo
thankful for a glass of
que agradecer un vaso de
water be this you want me to be
agua sea esto queréis que
thankful for this you want me to be
agradezca esto queréis que
thankful for But what is the next thing I am
agradezca Pero qué es lo próximo que
thankful for good
agradezco los buenos
morning Yes,
días Eso
thank you very much for your c
sí muchas gracias por tus c
members
miembros
applause applause applause to the entire
aplauso un aplauso un aplauso a todo el
chat
chat
for the neighborhood for
para el barrio para
you thank you very much
ti muchas gracias
[ __ ] Like yes [ __ ] like that we are here
cabrón Así sí [__] así sí estamos aquí
man 17 people 300 on
tío 17 personas 300 en
Twitch if everyone gave c we would
Twitch si todo el mundo regalaran c
be here quietly almost 10,000
seríamos aquí tranquilamente casi 10000
members
miembros
no and the day [ __ ] if I have to
no y el día [__] si es que tengo que
be like this all the time uncle
estar así todo el tiempo
calm down grandpa no calm down grandpa
tío tranquilo abuelo no tranquilo abuelo
no man it is not normal it is not
no tío es que no es normal es que no es
normal here Look Sharon Natalia look and she
normal está Mira Sharon Natalia mira y
will want me to thank the aunt that
querrá que le d las gracias a la tía que
laugh give her grace too
rer le deas gracia también
eh [ __ ] already man each one five members
eh [__] ya hombre cada uno cinco miembro
20 members damn there in full force let
20 miembros [__] ahí a saco que se note
the power be seen Look Jer a kiss gorgeous let
el poderío Mira Jer un beso guapísimo se
the power of the kids be seen if
note el poderío de la chavalería que
I arrive tomorrow at telesalseo and tell
llegue yo mañana a telesalseo y le diga
the lady
a la señora
lady that I'm quitting my job okay I'm quitting my
señora que dejo el trabajo vale que dejo
job I'm quitting
el trabajo lo dejo
everything why because I have 5000 members
todo por qué porque tengo 5000 miembros
in the little one I'm not even coming around here anymore
en el canijo Yo por aquí ya ni me paso
lady okay That depends on you a
señora vale Eso depende de ustedes un
kiss Mike
beso Mike
gorgeous bunch of
guapísimo montón de
people watch out with the joke If everyone
gente ojo que con la broma Si todos
donates a member you reach 3000
donan un miembro llegas a los 3000
members But what are they going to donate what are they going to
miembros Pero qué van a donar qué van a
donate what are they going to donate girl aren't you
donar qué van a donar chiquilla no les
seeing that they're making fun
Estás viendo que se están cachondeando
of us mait what are they
de nosotros mait que se están
making fun of us Javi you have more
cachondeando de nosotros Javi tienes más
members than other channels of the rabble
miembros que otros canales de la chusma
feel good who are you referring to with the
siéntete bien a quién te refieres con la
rabble with the
chusma con la
rabble but I'm not measuring myself against
chusma pero yo no me estoy midiendo con
anyone only with the chocas Who are you
nadie solo con el chocas A quién te
referring to with the rabble I'm not
refieres con la chusma yo no me estoy
measuring myself against anyone only with the chocas
midiendo con nadie yo solo con el chocas
How much does the chocas have right now if I
Cuánto tiene el chocas ahora mismo si os
have to  insult one by one I'm going to
tengo que insultar uno por uno os voy a
insult you one by one eh To have the
insultar uno por uno eh Para tener lo
same How
mismo Cuánto tiene el chocas ahora
much does Chostas have right now How much does
mismo Cuánto tiene el
Chostas have I want you to
chocas yo quiero que me
spit on me No man with five bucks no with
escupas No hombre con cinco pavos no con
five bucks I won't spit on you it's okay it's
cinco pavos no te escupo está bien está
okay glo How much does Chostas have
bien glo Cuánto tiene el chocas ahora
right now nobody knows Look look look look look look this is
mismo nadie sabe Mira mira mira mira
a disgrace or so
mira mira esto una vergüenza o sea esto
these C of disgrace These are
estos C de de la vergüenza Estos son
click with those who laugh at us on
click con los que se ríen de nosotros en
Twitter in x then
Twitter en x luego
okay These are t who laugh at us the
vale Estos son t que se ríen de nosotros
people How much does Chostas have nobody
la gente Cuánto tiene el choca nadie lo
knows Maite Thank you Hi if it weren't for you
sabe Maite Gracias Hi si no fuera por ti
this would be a disgrace
esto sería una vergüenza
Maite How much does
Maite Cuánto tiene el
Chostas have I'm already without a voice eh I've been
chocas ya me quedo sin voz eh Ya llevo 5
live for 5 hours not even the hour because you're
horas en directo ni la hora por
ungrateful Damian screw you Damian screw
desagradecido Damián que te den Damián
you
que te den
nobody knows how much does
nadie sabe cuánto tiene el
Chostas have nobody knows it's for today it's for
chocas nadie sabe es para hoy es para
today guys it's for
hoy chavales es para
today for today guys nobody tells me Lu
hoy para hoy chavales nadie me dice Lu
Tell me t son if you don't tell me
Dímelo t hijo que si no me lo dices tú
nobody tells me Lu informs us a
no me lo dice nadie Lu nos informa un
Look they have been made  over there
Mira se han hecho por ahí
subscriber Prim
suscriptor Prim
Prim member a kiss Francisco
Prim miembro un beso Francisco
Welcome to the
Bienvenido a la
family B given away one Vic has given away
familia B regalado uno vic ha regalado
a member Thank you very much Vic thank you very much let's
un miembro Muchas gracias vic muchas
see nobody says nobody knows
gracias a ver nadie lo dice nadie sabe
how much Chocas has 500,000 no no no
cuánto tiene el chocas 500.000 no no no
more than 10,000 Alexo 50 members like that yes like that yes we
más de 10.000 alexo 50 miembros así sí
arrived man Alexos Alexos how much did it cost you tell us Alexo how much did it
así sí llegamos hombre
cost you tell them
dilo alexo cuánto te ha costado
how much did it cost you Alexo tell us
dilos cuánto te ha costado alexo dínoslo
and they spoke to me a group of artists
y me hablaron una banda de artistas me
told me Good thing you said it because
dijeron Menos mal que lo dijiste porque
nobody dared to say it and we all thought it
nadie se animaba a decirlo y todos lo
28 28 cost 50 members now
28 28 cuestan 50 miembros ahora
Alexo [ __ ] give away
alexo cabrón regala
100 this looks like a
100 esto parece un canal de
telesales channel Chocas has 46,000 right now
televentas 46000 tiene el chocas ahora
Oh no 14,000 14,000 14,000 guys it's done it's
mismo Ah no 14000 14000 14000 chavales
done
se hace se hace
easily 14,000 it's done
facilito 14000 se hace
easily 14,000 14,000 it's done
facilito 14000 14000 se hace
easily
facilito
14000 members makes it easy, guys,
14000 miembros hace facilito cabrones
we're 18
somos 18
people, we fit seven or members
personas cabemos a siete O miembros cada
each, literally, the apple
uno literal está rep podrida la manzana
of the scene is really rotten. So when
de la escena rep podrida Entonces cuando
one jumps out, it rots. So to speak, since it's
salta uno pudrirla Por así decirlo como
already really rotten, everyone agrees with him.
ya está rep podrida todos le dan la
Wave: Ah, good thing you beat her.
razón onda Ah Menos mal que la batiste
Good thing you told her, leral. I'm not
Menos mal que se lo dijiste leral yo no
going to give names. Because I don't want to
voy a dar nombre Porque no quiero
expose anyone because I understand that
exponer a nadie porque entiendo de los
artists are throwing away, you lack humility, says
artistas tirar te falta humildad dice
Ariel. Ariel, what for? What's that for?
Ariel Ariel para qué Para qué sirve eso
Ariel. But how? What humility if they're
Ariel Pero cómo Que humildad si te están
giving you a member, a member, a
regalando un miembro un miembro un
member, a member. How are you not going to
miembro un miembro Cómo no les vas a
insult them? Humility, nor humility, is
insultar la peña humildad ni humildad es
that a fact? It's really dangerous, nobody says
esa un facto Es rep peligroso nadie dice
anything, really lukewarm. Well, us
nada re tibio bueno nosotros los
streamers can do it without a problem. They
streamer podemos hacerlo sin problema se
laugh at our careers, they laugh at what
ríen de nuestra carrera se ríen de lo
we do. They say we have no talent,
que hacemos dicen que no tenemos talento
that we live off of something else, well, let's
que vivimos de vimos de lo otro bueno a
see. I would have kept a lot of
ver yo me hubiera guardado un montón de
things to myself and shared them in my
cosas y las hubiera compartido en en el
inner circle, that is, I would have spoken
círculo íntimo es decir hubiera hablado
to that person and tried to make myself
con esa persona y hubiera tratado de
understood, I understand, or
llegar a un hacerme entender entend o
rather, to reach out.  to understand what was
mejor dicho llegar a entender qu era lo
happening I would have
que estaba pasando me lo hubiera
kept it to myself I would have
guardado para para la intimidad hubiera
fixed these problems behind closed doors
arreglado estos problemas puertas para
when I saw that it was impossible and the
dentro cuando vi que era imposible y me
same thing happened to me three times I said okay okay okay
pasó las tres veces lo mismo dije okay
okay And when the straw
okay okay okay Y cuando llegó la la gota
that broke the camel's back came Fando
que rebalsó el vaso
made fun of Alo that it wasn't for
fando se hiz car de Alo que no era para
her and I peed but I peed there I said
ella y meardi pero me reard ahí dije
ready dude [ __ ] I'm going to try to
listo boludo [__] voy a intentar
fix it with people who and I'll have to start
arreglar con gente que y tend que armar
a war a kiss Sorita a kiss
una guerra un beso sorita un beso
sweetheart long live Argentina get back yourselves the
corazón viva Argentina repórtense los
Argentinians out there look at you
argentinos por ahí mira ar repórtense
Argentinians get back yourselves out there because
los argentinos por ahí porque se está
a war is starting all the fans
Armando una guerra estn todos los fand
fighting against now all of Twitter And
peleando contra ahora todo Twitter La y
well there will be a war dude it's
bueno habrá una guerra boludo está
rekindling the community dude that's
reavivando la comunidad boludo eso es
key for me and I didn't do it That's why I did
clave para mí y no lo hice Por esto yo
n't I didn't do it all this that happened didn't
no yo no hice lo todo esto que pasó no
happen because I had a strategy it happened
pasó porque yo tenía una estrategia pasó
because they pissed me off you understand to
porque me tocaron las pelotas entendés a
an extreme point it didn't happen because I
un punto ya extremo no pasó porque yo
said with this revive the c it didn't happen that's why it
dije con esto revive la c no pasó por
could have also happened that they
eso también podría haber pasado que me
all let go of my hand and said what does
soltaban la mano todos y decían qué se
this idiot think he is, cursing the
cree este pelotido bardeando a los
artists and those who supported him says it didn't happen
artistas y que le apoyaron dice no pasó
because I said with this revive the m it didn't
porque yo dije con esto revive la m no
happen that's why it could also have happened
pasó por eso también podría haber pasado
that they all let go of my hand and said
que me soltaban la mano todos y decían
what does this pilot think by pairing the
qué se cree este piloo pareando a los
artists and they all turned against me
artistas y todos se ponían en contra mía
but since I'm already used to
pero como yo ya estoy acostumbrado a
flirting for free I sucked an egg I
ligar de gratis me chupado un huevo lo
did it anyway he lives in his own world totally
hice igual vive en su mundo totalmente
eh Javi if you're going to insult start
eh Javi si vas a insultar empieza
insulting me [ __ ] off wiar you
insultándome a mí Vete a la [__] wiar
have me fed up with get out of
que me tienes hasta la [__] vete de
here I don't know what the [ __ ] you're doing here it was a
aquí no sé qué [__] hace aquí era un
chance it could happen Anything pisses me
azar podía pasar Cualquier cosa me da
off that I always have to be the one
bronca que siempre tenga que ser yo el
who jumps they're all lukewarm all Cab In
que salta son todos tibios todos Cab De
fact I know a streamer gang that
hecho yo conozco una banda de streamer
the weirdos And none of them dare to
que los raron Y ninguno se anima a
confront the artists the weirdos
enfrentar a los artistas los raron
none of them I know a
ninguno yo conozco a una banda de
streamer gang here what he's trying to
streamer aquí lo que está intentando
say correct me if I'm wrong is that
decir corregirme si me equivoco es que
they
los
used them okay they used them they
utilizaron vale que los utilizaron los
caught them by the point okay they started to confront them they
cogieron de punto vale se an enfrentar
did things on the
los hicieron cosas
network and in the chat they surely know dees
red y en el chat seguramente saben dees
Hi I was talking about I looked for but and
Hi estaba hablando de I buscaron pero y
for the face a kiss Chava collection
por la cara un beso colección de Chava
Put your member where  you Uy That can't be
Métete el miembro donde te Uy Eso no se
said they're going to p me I'm
puede decir me van a p
going crazy man I'm
un se me está yendo la olla tío se me
going crazy I'm getting carried away
está yendo la olla me estoy viniendo
Thanks Alexos thanks Lurbin
arriba Gracias alexos gracias lurbin
thanks Kevin thanks Palom thanks
gracias Kevin gracias palom gracias
Giordano Thank you so much to all of you
Giordano Muchísimas gracias a todos los
who are giving away members in
que estáis regalando miembros en
conditions Thank you so much
condiciones Muchísimas gracias
to just gave away 20 it seems to me
a acaba de regalar 20 me aparecen a mí
that he has given away I don't know if it's true or
que ha regalado no sé si será verdad o
not but it seems to me that they have given away sales
no pero me apece que han regalado ventes
that way it will get lively man that way it will get
así sí se anima esto hombre así sí se
lively what can't be is that they are
anima lo que no puede ser es que estén
giving away one by one ibai and Spring
regalando de uno en uno ibai y Spring
with Nicki Nicole because ibai ivai and
con Nicki Nicole porque ibai ivai y
Sprint both ibai and Sprint have
Sprint tanto ibai como Sprint han
collaborated with Nicki Nicole so
colaborado con Nicki Nicole entonces
here koku is sleeping with her I and Sprint
aquí koku se la está tirando I y Sprint
eh watch out
eh ojito
eh be without a filter without a [ __ ] filter more
eh sea sin filtro sin [__] filtro más
anger because you see they are younger me I
bronca porque lo ves son más chicos yo
don't do it to me I play
yo a mí no me la a mí yo me hago el
dumb but I see everything they are not
boludo pero yo veo todo a mí no me la
going to do it to me and if they do I will shut my
van a hacer y si me la hacen cierro el
ass and gave away 10 instead of 20
[__] y regaló 10 en vez de 20
Ah only  gave away 10 instead of 20 your friend
Ah solo regaló 10 en vez de 20 tu pana
So you have to give away another 10
Entonces tienes que regalar otros 10
friend I was
amigo que me he
wrong give away another 10 or pay me back
equivocado regala otros 10 o devuelveme
thanks Okay, ready, watch out here I already
gracias Bueno listo ojo acá yo ya me di
realized there are other p that are younger,
cuenta hay otros p que son más jóvenes
more chic and he passes it
más chic y lo pasa por
over Okay, I don't know what
arriba Bueno pues no sé que habéis
you have checked here, I don't know what
comprobado ustedes aquí no sé que habéis
you have seen here but I have seen I have
visto ustedes aquí pero yo he visto
seen a c a little a little
a yo he visto a un c un poco un poco
overbearing a little
sobrado un poco
overbearing okay And I think
sobrado vale Y yo opino
that about this video that we have seen,
que sobre este vídeo que hemos visto
thank you very much I will see opinions about this video
gracias a veré opinis sobre este vídeo
that we have
que hemos
seen op okay that's what we are here for I
visto op vale que para eso estamos aquí
think that this video that we have seen
Yo opino que este vídeo que hemos visto
is
es
nice put it about Dallas no no I don't feel like
bonito ponlo de Dallas no no no me da la
putting it about Dallas yet we
gana todavía de ponerlo de Dallas lo
will see it
vamos a ver
later I have to follow the order
después yo tengo que seguir el orden
here of the outline okay of the
aquí de la escaleta vale de de la
outline that makes places for me that's what
escaleta que me hace lugares que para
the content director is for okay And we ca
eso es el director de contenido vale Y
n't forget this tweet that
no se nos puede olvidar este twet que ha
c has posted we can't forget this one that he
puesto c no se nos puede olvidar este
posted I literally have 70
que ha puesto tengo literalmente al 70
percent of the scene congratulating me and
por de la escena felicitándome y
thanking me  from what I said that's
agradeciéndome por lo que dije eso
also a fake it's the tail for
también es caretaje es la cola para que
us to spit on er Javi brilliant heart you
nos escupa er Javi corazón brillante eso
already put that before no you
ya lo pusiste antes
already put that before
no eso ya lo pusiste antes
no Sofia Thank you so much
no Sofía Muchísimas gracias
beautiful Sofia Cabrera has given away cco
guapísima Sofía Cabrera ha regalado cco
and also one Thank you very much
y también uno Muchas gracias
Sofia that's how we get there man That way we could
Sofía así sí llegamos tío Así podríamos
reach 100,000 members today
llegar hoy mismo a los 100000 miembros
if I don't want much
si es que yo tampoco quiero mucho
more either if I don't ask for much
más si es que yo tampoco pido mucho
more in the end it didn't suit the c
más al final no le venía nada bien al c
Well let's see the next
Bueno a ver la siguiente
move lai mid has prepared for me
movida lai mid me ha preparado
here the next move that
aquí la siguiente movida que me ha
luare has prepared for me here I think it's a bit
preparado aquí luare creo que es un poco
senseless no but well if people
sin sentido no pero bueno si la gente
are speculating on Twitter
está especulando en Twitter
eh we can see it eh
eh lo podemos ver eh
6.70 euros in
6.70 eur en
Argentina
Argentina
6.70 in Argentina are worth 10 members
6.70 en Argentina valen 10 miembros
6.70 in Argentina why are you repeating it to me you've
6.70 en Argentina por qué me lo repite
seen my face Hello Javi It's the first
me ha visto cara Hola Javi Es la primera
time I've become a member of a channel Haha I
vez que me hago miembro de un canal Jaja
don't really know how this goes greetings
No sé muy bien Cómo va esto un saludo
from Honduras I'm a woman wish me luck
desde Honduras soy mujer deséame suerte
with my pregnancy because I'm having a
en mi embarazo que la estoy pasando un
bit of a bad time you just told me  your whole
poco mal me acabas de contar toda tu
life you just told me your whole life I
vida me acabas de contar toda tu vida o
mean you just told me eh that it's the
sea me acabas de contar eh que es la
first time they made you a member of a
primera vez que te hacen miembro de un
channel that you don't know how this works that you
canal que no sabes cómo funciona esto
live in Honduras that you're a woman I mean
que vives en Honduras que eres mujer o
now it turns out that I asked for your
sea ahora resulta que te he pedido el
ID, not me and that you're pregnant
dni yo no y que estás embarazada
Giordano Thank you very much you
Giordano Muchas gracias
just told me your whole life I don't know
me acabas de contar toda tu vida no sé
teos your friend now we are at peace
teos tu pana ahora sí estamos en paz
Thank you very much your friend your friend I already
Muchísimas gracias tu pana tu pana yo ya
you already today you have fulfilled okay you can
tú ya hoy has cumplido vale tú puedes
stop lurbin I don't care just kidding
parar lurbin no me importa es broma
joking lurbin I always wish you the best
broma lurbin Te deseo lo mejor siempre
all the kids we wish you good
toda la chavalería te deseamos mucha
luck with the pregnancy and please
suerte en el embarazo y por favor
let us know when you have it okay the
Avísanos cuando lo tengas vale todo el
whole chat the whole chat applause applause
chat todo el chat un aplauso un aplauso
for lurd okay apart donated not how are
para lurd vale aparte donado no como
you there acting like an idiot in the
edes ahí haciendo el [__] en el
chat Well let's see what Ricky eddy does
chat Bueno vamos a ver lo de Ricky edy
let's see what Ricky Eddy does it turns out that
vamos a ver lo de Ricky Eddy resulta que
according to what luare tells me here there would
según que me pone por aquí luare se
be speculation there would be
estaría especulando se estaría
speculation because Ricky uploaded a
especulando porque Ricky ha subido una
photo with a friend okay the strangest thing let's
foto con una amiga vale lo más extraño a
see let's read it  what turns me on Here
ver vamos a leer lo que me pone Aquí
luare let's read it in full what
luare vamos a leerlo completo lo que me
turns me on luar yesterday was the birthday of this
pone luar ayer fue el cumpleaños de esta
girl named Sira which she celebrated with
chica llamada Sira el cual celebró con
Ricky at a well known nightclub in
Ricky en una conocida discoteca de
Badalona she uploaded some photos with Ricky to
badalona subió algunas fotos con Ricky a
her Instagram the strange thing is that Ricky
su Instagram lo extraño es que Ricky
decided to upload them not to his Instagram
haya decidido subirlas no a su Instagram
but directly to Twitter with a
sino directamente a Twitter con un
heart Knowing what it would provoke on
corazón Sabiendo lo que provocaría en
Twitter and tagging the girl in the
Twitter y etiquetando a la chica en el
tweet well please
twit bueno por favor
dude 2023
tío 2023
guys 2023
chavales 2023
guys but what is a
chavales pero que es una
photo Well can you stop with the whole thing of
foto Bueno podéis dejar rollito de ir
giving away members one by one
regalando miembros de uno a uno por
please and give them away 50 to 50 I ask I ask
favor y regalarlo de 50 a 50 pregunto
ok I ask it stopped being
pregunto vale pregunto dejo de hacer
funny Half an
gracia Hace media
hour ago it stopped being funny Half an
hora dejó de hacer gracia Hace media
hour ago anyone is better than Ali
hora cualquiera es mejor que el Ali
Draco but man no don't make
Draco pero hombre no no hagas
comparisons that's very sexist don't
comparaciones que eso es muy machiste no
make comparisons please
hagas comparaciones por favor las
women don't compare themselves it's not the
mujeres no se comparan no son los
prices at Mercadona with the day let's see
precios del mercadona con el día a ver
let's see but if it's a photo with a
vamos a ver pero si es una foto con una
friend dude I have photos too man
amiga tío yo tengo fotos también hombre
I have photos with many friends Let's
yo tengo fotos con muchas amigas A
see it's okay I recently uploaded
ver no pasa nada Hace poco subí
one precisely this  and well they started putting gu I don't
una esta y bueno empezaron a poner gu no
know what they also started with the
sé qué empezaron también con las
nonsense not the collection of girls I don't
tonterías no la colección de chavas no
even know how long you've been today but thank you very
sé ni cuánto llevas hoy pero muchas
much Thank you very much This is one
gracias Muchísimas gracias Esta es una
of my two best friends Okay I have two
de mis dos mejores amigas Vale tengo dos
best friends well this one is like if she
mejores amigas pues esta es una como si
were my sister I mean it's that I love them
fuera mi hermana o sea es que las quiero
very much and I adore her compare Yes well it's
muchísimo y la adoro compara Sí pues
also true al it's also true no I mean
también es verdad al también es verdad
nothing happens I mean imagine
no O sea no pasa nada O sea imagínate
that I upload this photo on Twitter and I
que subo esta foto en Twitter y la
tag her because I feel like it
etiqueto porque me da la
okay I mean please they are photos let's
gana vale o sea por favor que son fotos
see they are not eating each other's mouths
a ver no se están comiendo la boca
either no
tampoco
women are not compared
no las mujeres no se comparan las
women
mujeres
bill Let's see it's a photo and she says the
facturan A ver es una foto y dice lo más
strangest thing is that she responds to the tweet
extraño es que ella le responde al tweet
with an I love you and then after someone
con un te amo y luego de que alguien le
asks her how do you love each other in less than a month
pregunte cómo se ama en menos de un mes
Ricky says that they were friends since But
Ricky diga que fueran colega desde Pero
what's so strange about it
qué es lo que tiene too de raro por
please luare what did you
favor luare qué me has
put to me then Ricky Ed blocks me of course he gets
puesto luego Ricky Ed me bloquea claro
offended he says I love you and says how do you love each other
se ofende le dice te amo y dice cómo se
in less than a month and he says Ricky
ama en menos de un mes y le dice Ricky
being friends for 8 years of course
siendo colegas desde hace 8 años claro
man it seems that they have known each other since
hombre se ve que sí se conocen desde
before a
antes
But what was this dude what was this
a Pero qué era esto tío qué ha sido este
extract dude Sofia
extracto tío Sofía
Cabrera what was this extract dude I'm
Cabrera qué ha sido este extracto tío lo
going to monetize it anyway eh What happens is we
voy a monetizar igual eh Lo que pasa que
didn't get to 8 minutes what can we
no llegamos a 8 minutos qué podemos
do in these three left
hacer en est en estos tres que quedan
for it to reach 8 the
para que llegue a 8 el
extract with Lali also knew each other from
extracto con Lali también se conocía de
8 years ago Good point I can insult you
hace 8 años Buen punto te puedo insultar
[ __ ] [ __ ] now I'm going to give 1000 bits
[__] subnormal ya ya voy a dar 1000 bits
to put myself above V bre the SIM
para ponerme por encima de V bre el SIM
of nimu poim with love cheers up with the
de nimu poim con cariño ánimo con la
night Javi Greetings from
noche Javi Saludos desde
Vienna Sofia
Viena Sofía
Sofia you just cut my roll girl
Sofía me acabas de cortar el rollo tía
I was
estaba yo
happy Wow let's see if I get on Twitch
contento Wow a ver que me meta en Twitch
for
para
that let's see if I get on Twitch to see
eso a ver que me meta en Twitch a ver
who's first on the
quién está primero en el
channel my goodness the joke you guys have
canal madre mía el cachondeo que tenéis
with a member I don't
con lo de un miembro Yo es que ya no sé
even know how long we've been going Let's see wait and see the
ni cuánto llevamos A ver espérate a ver
Twitch Stream manager thing But
lo de Twitch gestor del Stream Pero
anyway stop with the
bueno parar ya con el rollo de un
member thing no let's see but that
miembro no a ver pero eso eso del
ranking thing where can you
ranking dónde se
see that ranking where does it come out I'm going to
ve eso del ranking dónde sale voy a
put myself at the top of V brep the s of
ponerme por lo alto de V brep el s de
nimu But  that where does it say I would have to
nimu Pero eso dónde sale me tendría que
log into my channel
meter en mi canal
not go back to
no volver a
Twitch
Twitch
channel channel
canal canal
silence my [ __ ] voice which is uglier than
silencio mi [__] voz que es más fea que
[ __ ] I don't even know how you hear me
una [__] no sé ni cómo me escucháis
where does that
dónde sale eso del
ranking come from where does that
ranking dónde sale eso el
ranking come from Roman Thank you very much where does the
ranking Román Muchas gracias dónde sale
ranking come from where does it say
lo del ranking dónde lo
buy bit chat from the Stream give away
pone comprar bit chat del Stream regalar
a subscription Oh I see it I see it I
una suscripción Ah ya lo veo ya lo veo
see it Okay so the first one is
ya lo veo Vale pues la la primera está
lampur lampur Isaac with 15 members that I
lampur lampur Isaac con 15 miembros que
also tell you lampur It's not worth
también te digo lampur Tampoco es para
showing off either eh It's not worth tearing your
vasilar eh Tampoco es para romperte la
shirt off you have to Salt the buttons then there
camisa hay que Salt los botones luego
's Bred the SIM from nimu The SIM from
está Bred el SIM de nimu El SIM de
nimu with 1300 who is also a bit
nimu con 1300 que también da un poco de
scary holding a nimu s here for
cosa aguantando aquí un s de nimu por
1300 Feet would also piss me off a bit
1300 Feet también me jodería un poco
quite a bit no and then sm carrera with 500
bastante no y luego sm carrera con 500
well let's see you guys give a bit of a scare what can I
bueno a ver dais un poco de cosilla qué
say Hey everyone who's
os digo Oye todos los que me estáis
watching me from Twitch follow me too
viendo desde Twitch seguirme también
follow me too on Twitch Uh how many
seguirme también en Twitch Eh cuántos
followers are we on Twitch Well on
seguidores somos en Twitch Pues en
Twitch we are
Twitch somos ahora
60,000 right now We've reached  60,000
mismo 60.000 Hemos llegado a 60.000
you 60,000 followers
tú 60.000 seguidores
you say someone says a certain Rosana jav
tú dice alguien dice una tal Rosana jav
not everyone has more Rosana It's
no todo el mundo tiene para más Rosana
not my problem it's not my problem
No es mi problema no es mi problema
honey I'll tell you my life It's not my
cariño yo te cuento mi vida No es mi
problem Rosana the truth don't come here
problema Rosana la verdad no vengas aquí
crying I don't care about the subject
llorando a mí no me importa el tema a mí
your voice entertains me a lot and when you
me entretiene mucho tu voz y cuando
say now I tell you now I tell you what at
dices ahora te digo ahora te digo qué at
turum well Okay come on we have 8
turum bueno Vale venga ya tenemos 8
minutes
minutos
Ricky unblock me come on Javier canijo we
Ricky desbloquéame veng a Javier canijo
do an interview
hacemos una entrevista
and say it Hash Javi Oliveira was right
y dilo Hash Javi oliveira tenía razón
from the first day
desde el primer día
okay I really I really love you
vale Yo en verdad Yo en verdad te quiero
a little Ricky let's
un poco Ricky a
see let's see let's see let's see let's
ver a ver a ver a ver a ver a ver a
see
ver
Tercel
Tercel
third third And
tercer tercer Y
probably third And probably
probablemente tercer Y probablemente
last extract of the
último extracto de la
night f in the chat yes yes yes yes yes yes
noche f en el chat sí
more time with
sí sí sí sí sí más tiempo con música de
intro music than live yes I am I can I can
intro que de directo sí soy puedo puedo
afford it autu
permitírmelo autu Muchas
Thank you very much I don't know I don't ask for
gracias No no sé yo no pido
explanations from you How about last I
explicaciones a ustedes Cómo que útimo
don't know the truth look for yourselves it depends
no sé la verdad buscaros la vida depende
on you eh it depends on you too
de ustedes eh depende de ustedes también
time is money dude time is money eh
el tiempo es oro tío el tiempo es oro eh
time is money guys it depends on how
el tiempo es oro chavales depende de cóm
the night goes it depends on how this
vaya la noche depende de cóm vaya este
last extract goes and it seems to me that it won't be
último extracto y me parece que no será
very long Javi scammer I'm sorry your
muy largo Javi estafador Lo siento sus
the truth don't insult me I don't
la verdad no me insultes Yo tampoco te
disrespect you either to see the YouTube account in the
respeto a ver la cuenta de YouTube al
end it's mine no and the computer too
final es mía no y el ordenador también
no
no
terrible grandpa but it's that no I don't know
terrible abuelo pero es que no no sé
you're very critical eh I also tell you
sois muy criticones eh También os digo
eh you're very critical dude I mean
eh sois muy criticones tío o sea es que
120 members so far this
120 miembros en lo que va de
night and on top of that I've had to eat on the
noche y encima he tenido que comer la
street like any worker Alex a
calle como cualquier currante Alex un
kiss you haven't even paid me today it
beso no me habéis pagado hoy ni la
's 120 members of
dietas son 120 miembros de
latan goal minimum of 5000 mi of course Those
latan meta mínimo de 5000 mi claro Esas
are the aspirations that
son las aspiraciones que tenemos
anyone has in
cualquiera la
life Those are the aspirations that
vida Esas son las aspiraciones que
anyone should have Hey 120
tenemos que tener cualquiera Oye 120
members to listen to music is fine
miembros para escuchar música está bien
no no don't make any mistake only they haven't
no no no te equivoques only que no me
given me anything in a
han dado nada en una hora
whole hour in a whole hour take lampur
entera en una hora entera toma lampur
to put myself above
para ponerme más por encima del SIM de
nimu's SIM don't me Funes Javi that tomorrow I have to
nimu no me Funes Javi que mañana tengo
work I'm not a youtuber Just kidding
que trabajar no soy youtuber Es broma
buddy pochi  My Love
colega pochi My Love
damn
ostia
but he's not here Today no br is not here the s
pero no está aquí Hoy no br no está el s
of n is not here
de n no está aquí
Today
Hoy
[Music]
[Música]
no no
no
and Romn with a Romn member Shut up
no y Román con un miembro Román Cállate
How are you going to give away a Rom member if
Cómo vas a regalar un miembro romá si
the girl is pregnant and won't stop
está la chavala embarazada y no para de
donating man look Look for the pregnant women
donar tío mira Mira por las mujeres
man Look for the pregnant women man
tío Mira por las mujeres embarazadas tío
oppressor the
opresor no está el
Bred is not here the Bred is not here today
Bred no está el Bred hoy aquí
eh Well my goodness how did they just
eh Pues madre mía comoo lo acaban de
humiliate him Eh well let's
humillar Eh bueno a
see let's go to the other simp of
ver vamos al otro simp de
nimu
nimu
delox just kidding just kidding just kidding joke joke joke joke
delox es broma es broma es broma broma
delox joke very
broma broma broma delox broma humor muy
dark humor very dark humor okay let's see this
negro humor muy negro vale a ver esto
This image What
Esta imagen Qué
is this image What is nimu with a
es esta imagen Qué es nimu con un
balaclava with three YouTube plates and
pasamontaña con tres placas de YouTube y
a
una de
gold one touching
oro tocándole la carita al
delox's face
delox
today nimu published his last live with
hoy nimu publicó su último directo con
delox in which they explained when
delox en el cual explicaron Cuándo sale
the debate comes out and delox tried to give some
el debate y delox intentó dar algunos
spoilers Although nimu hasn't
spoilers Aunque nimu no es que le haya
allowed him to give many since nimu didn't
permitido dar muchos ya que nimu no lo
let him speak practically throughout the entire
dejó hablar prácticamente en todo el
live he also commented on the podcast he
directo también comentó el podcast que
will do with
hará con
And how he will try to be  nominated for the
Y cómo intentará estar nominado a los
eslam awards also says he hopes to
premios eslam además dice que espera
soon have more guests from Latin America like
pronto tener más invitados de latan como
Dross and people from Spain like El Rubius
Dross y a gente de España como El Rubius
mpg really I mean what a drag
mpg de verdad O sea qué pereza
mpg what a drag
mpg qué pereza
mpg it's already 2:30 in the morning the
mpg ya son las 2:30 de la mañana ya la
joke is on me I have to comb my hair and I don't have a gum No
broma tengo que peinar y no tengo gom No
man Alex no no no no no with 200 B
hombre Alex no no no no no con 200 B Se
You are loved with 200 B You are appreciated you are
te quiere con 200 B Se te aprecia se te
appreciated and you and you are valued it's not nm I will touch I will
aprecia y se te y se te valora no es nm
touch the legs of this
tocaré tocaré las pernas de este corazón
excited heart I will touch the face of my
ilusionado tocaré la carita de mi
delox who is
delox que está
excited with the bum I
emocionado con el bum
miss Ivan But why Why is
se extraña el Iván Pero por qué Por qué
Ivan missed Let's see explain to me
se extraña el Iván A ver explícame por
why Alexander But why is
qué Alexander Pero por qué se extraña el
Ivan missed at what time of day when when when has he been
Iván en qué momento del día cuándo
missed is Ivan missed Why
extrañado se extraña el Iván Por qué por
why listen listen listen
qué escucha escucha escucha escucha
automatically that I am seeing him here
automáticamente que lo estoy viendo aquí
on the screen eh that I am seeing him here
en pantalla eh que lo estoy viendo aquí
on the screen
en pantalla
automatically right now Okay right now
automáticamente ahora mismo Vale ahora
and
mismo y ya
we'll see we'll see what happens next right
veremos ya veremos qué pasa después
now just as I give it  a Play
ahora mismo tal y como yo le de a Play
the video just as I press Play on the
al vídeo tal y como yo le de al Play del
video you have to press the
vídeo tenéis que darle al botón de
subscribe button those of you who are not subscribed
suscribirse los que no estéis suscritos
okay those of you who are subscribed don't give it
vale los que estéis suscritos no le deis
sons of [ __ ] that it will unsubscribe those of you who
hijos de [__] que se vaya a quitar los
are not subscribed to the Channel press the
que no estéis suscritos al Canal puls el
like button cheer no way it will be time to comb
botón de like cheer ni modo tocará
your hair humble Greetings from Catalonia
peinarse humilde Saludos desde Cataluña
my weapon a kiss Alex great Catalonia
mi arma un beso Alex grande Cataluña
great the Catalan eh I can't wait to
grande el Catalán eh estoy deseando de
go to Andorra to live to learn
irme a andorra a vivir para aprender
Catalan quite pathetic this live
Catalán bastante penoso este directo
begging for
mendigando
subs
subs
[Music]
[Música]
and Myself What to the
and Myself What to the
last r with my for Never turn Back again It's
last r with my for Never turn Back again
kind of fun that the more we Time
It's kind of fun that the more we Time
the more to rewind
the more to rewind
and to leave you but now I'm seeing all
and to leave you but now I'm seeing all
the
the
Sign this I ca
Sign
n't believe It's true I'm just as
this I can't believe It's true I'm just
surpris As
as surpris As
you
you
this I can't be to sure but I'll be
this I can't be to sure but I'll
[Music]
[Música]
[Applause] [
[Aplausos]
Again l in do the other 11 something from
Again l in do the other 11 something
Nothing I looking for an answer
from Nothing I looking for an answer
Maybe the biggest question was In The
Maybe the biggest question was In The
Last chapter  you gave me the soul I have to take
Last chapter you gave me the soul I have
without you I never could m
to take without you I never could m
that
ese
[ __ ] wanted to ban that idiot
[__] quería banear a ese imbécil
but of course
pero claro que voy a pedir suscriptores
I'm going to ask for subscribers my son what am I going to ask for? Of course I'm going to ask for subscribers my son what do you want me to ask for? Well look now I'm going to ask for it again everyone everyone everyone who is here it is mandatory on this channel it is mandatory
obligatorio en este canal es obligatorio
here it is no longer requested
aquí ya no se pide es
the subscribe button and the members button are mandatory I don't care
el botón de suscribiros y el de miembros
if you don't have money
me da igual que no tengáis dinero le
we stole from him to see real gossip I mean you
robábamos a ver salseo de verdad O sea
really have me fried Like this like this I'll
de verdad que me tenéis frito Así así
do it to you no because I'm going to do it like this you're going to
hago no porque voy a hacer así vas a
make some
hacer
dick like these p Tell him yes
pulgar porongas de estas p Dígale s
Tell him eh Tell him yes Tell him yes nimu is making fun of
Dígale s eh Díganle s Dígale s nimu se
delo nimu is making
está burlando de delo nimu se está
fun of
burlando de
delox
delox
look at him
míralo
Uf very clever the delox eh do this
Uf funadísimo el delox eh hacer esto
I am I'm going to become a
estoy me voy a hacer
streamer I don't disrespect my worthy
streamer no me falta respeto a mi digno
job fallen that G Stream for putting
trabajo cado que G Stream por poner
audio what the [ __ ] these lazy people these lazy people who do
audio qu [__] estos vagos estos vagos
n't work and earn  a
que no trabajan y ganan un
fortune No look at the point D is that
dineral No mira el el el punto D es que
you've already confused me, I mean more
me has despistado ya o sea más
literally confused where I wanted to go
literalmente despistado dónde quería ir
what you're commenting on, I don't know, it's a
qué le está comentando no sé es una
misplaced person and you put it again I was going
desubicada y lo vuelves a
to say something or rather Ah the
poner iba a decir algo o sea Ah el
spoiler look look is that you imagine that I
spoiler mira mira es que te imaginas que
screw up the spoiler of the debate by putting
les jodo el spoiler del debate por poner
a, I mean you imagine or I know I mean they
un o sea te imaginas o se es decir te
cut off your head they join you again you know let's
cortan la cabeza te junan de nuevoo
see they were saying that killing yourself could
ver decían de que matarse a pajas podía
cause memory loss and other
generar perdidas de memorias y otras
things that I don't
cosas que no
remember what
recuerdo qué
idiot was heard says Telox that
[__] se escucharon dice telox que
between Dallas that chat at that moment he didn't
entre Dallas que chat ese momento n
feel the true terror Now yes
sintió el verdadero terror Ahora sí
tell your spoiler let's see okay let's see the
conta tu spoiler a ver vale a ver el
spoiler come on [ __ ] leave it there with the
spoiler venga [__] dejaros ya ahí con la
little joke
bromita
spoilers we want
spoilers queremos
spoilers eh of course we are here with
spoilers eh claro estamos aquí con
Chernobyl internet tried
internet de chernobil intentado
Download the podcast because the podcast
Descargar el podcast porque el podcast
is always two parts Okay any
siempre son dos partes Vale cualquier
episode there is the teaser and the podcast worth
episodio hay el teaser y el podcast vale
the video so of course a lot of people
el vídeo entonces claro mucha gente se
believe that once we have the video already boom It comes
cree que una vez tenemos el vídeo ya pum
out tomorrow no no no no I mean the teaser
Sale Mañana no no no no O sea el teaser
is what always takes the longest
es lo que lleva más tiempo siempre
then  Let's say there's maybe a
entonces Ponle que a lo mejor queda una
week or something left because he can go at his own
semana o algo así porque puede ir a su
pace, no, there's still a week left
ritmo no que todavía queda una semana
Osa Of course, if it's the 18th,
Osa Claro si estamos a día 18 tenía que
the debate should have been today, it's true, the debate should have been
haber sido hoy el debate es verdad tenía
today, man, it's
que haber sido hoy el debate tío es
true So what's happening is that here we
verdad Entonces qué ocurre que aquí
have, since it's being processed
tenemos ya que se está procesando en
secretly for us to see, what is happening is,
oculto para verlo nosotros lo que viene
he's checking if it was for
el el est comprobando si era de
deaf-mutes or just for idiots, what you
sordomudos o solo de [__] lo que
're doing, I wanted to check that I
estás haciendo quería comprobar que
translated, I say, I think there's a deaf-mute
traducí digo creo que hay un sordo mudo
who's thinking that you just ordered
que está pensando que acabas de pedir
a four-cheese pizza, they
una pizza de cuatro quesos
already have the taser, they have the taser, you're done. You're
ya ya
done, can I continue?
estás Ya has acabado puedo seguir Ya se
The debate is cooling off, please? No
está enfriando el debate un po fav No
man, no no no, the debate is something
hombre no no no el debate es una cosa
that the same people are going to see, I think,
que la va a ver la misma gente yo creo
no no no, it's not that it's cooling off, no, I don't
no no no no es que se esté enfriando no
see it, I don't see it.
no lo veo no lo veo
[Music] It's
[Música]
bad that you can't
mal es que no se
because you want to invade,
puede por quieres invadir irá
FL FL will go, a
FL FL un
Catalan guy,
ca catal chicos
listen to the bus station, buses,
escuchen la estación de autobusos
buses, a
autobusos autobusos un
coffee is on. Catalan to go.  to
café está prendiendo Catalán para ir a
Andorra you know literally Well the point is
andorra sabes literal Pues el punto es
that there are both parts the part where
que hay las dos partes la parte donde
the debate is okay in itself that we can already
está el debate vale en sí que ya lo
see it ourselves to
podemos lo podremos ver nosotros para
see if it's good etcetera this may take
ver esté bien etcétera este puede que se
longer to upload than a
tarde más en subir que un episodio
normal episode because in the end it is a
normal porque al final es un formato
new format of course I think people do not
nuevo claro creo que la gente no
understand that it is not the same eh
entiende que no es lo no es lo mismo eh
this is going to take longer because we want it to be
esto vamos a tardar más porque queremos
very good because we know that it is
que esté muy bien porque sabemos que es
like the top episode and well people
como el episodio top y bueno la gente lo
are waiting for it and it is a format a
está esperando y es un formate un
completely new format because we are
formato completamente nuevo porque somos
three people I am moderator on
tres personas Yo estoy de moderador de
one side and then the two are there Dalas
un lado y luego los dos están ahí Dalas
yimu at all times which was also a very
yimu en todo momento que además fue muy
good choice to put you together because of the
buena elección poneros juntos porque la
memes that are going to come out of the two
de memes que van a salir de los dos
together the thing that is I can't you
juntos la de la de cosas que es no puedo
know look look I'm going to say one thing You
sabes mira mira voy a decir una cosa Tú
know I have many different coughs one is that
sabes que tengo muchos tos distintos uno
if they talk to me and I'm talking
es que si me hablan y yo estoy hablando
I shut up and the other is that if I'm
me callo y la otra es que si estoy
talking and they start doing
hablando y me empiezan a hacer técnicas
Naruto techniques on me I mean I get nervous
de Naruto O sea me pongo nervioso
so can we focus please I
entonces podemos centrarnos por favor
think I accidentally touched a tit
creo que he tocado una teta sin querer
the point No no no you didn't touch a tit
el punto No no no te tocaste una teta
but now everyone thinks you
pero ahora todo el mundo piensa que me
touched my
tocaste una
tit This is getting really hot
teta Esto se está poniendo muy caliente
no Hey Who has given away so many members
no Oye Quién ha regalado tantos miembros
Guardian
Guardián
Cosmo let's see but Who has given away so many
Cosmo a ver pero Quién ha regalado
members because it's sounding again so many
miembros porque está sonando otra ve
members or rather this is that
miembro o sea esto que es
Roman has given away another 50
que Roman ha regalado otros 50
members ROM ROM has given away another 50
miembros ROM ROM ha regalado otros 50
members we're talking about
miembros estamos hablando
if we do 200 members in this
que si hacemos 200 miembros en este
live or we're going to
directo o los vamos a
pass them it's Hot it's Hot the live yes No
pasar está Hot está Hot el directo sí No
man don't say that man it might upset her
hombre no digáis eso hombre que puede
girlfriend we're joking
sentarle mal la novia estamos de broma
but seriously No man they will
pero ya en serio No hombre tendrán
trust each other and it will be
confianza y será
fun Alexo gave away another 50
cachondeo alexo regaló otros 50
members well no me they don't appear here I mean it's being
miembros pues no me no me aparecen aquí
notified I can insult
o sea se está notificando puedo insultar
a
uno
[ __ ]
subnormal
you are a great one there are my bits
eres un grande al ahí tienes mis bits
to eat all the
para comerte todo el
cimbrel a little edge no lampur that you
cimbrel un poco borde no lampur que
're pregnant be imagine tomorrow the
estás embarazada sea imagínate mañana el
clip imagine tomorrow the clips of the
clip imagínate mañana los clips de los
haters jav oliveira forces pregnant to
hater jav oliveira obliga embarazada
eat him simbr for I know 10
comerle simbr por yo que sé 10
bucks Jos a kiss Thank you very much
pavos José un beso Muchísimas gracias
friend an applause an
amigo un aplauso un
applause  la to
aplauso la to
Then it's lucky they say you can't without
Entonces es suertudo dicen no puedes sin
wanting to okay I think they're just friends
querer vale Yo creo que solo son colegas
but they've had a lot of feeling in a short
pero han tenido mucho feeling en poco
time it's a
tiempo es un
fact like you with me
hecho como tú conmigo
alne pum colorada
alne pum colorada
colorada Thank you very much for giving away that
colorada Muchas gracias por regalar ese
subscriber alne like you with me
suscriptor se alne como tú conmigo
alne you and I like doing a live
alne tú y yo así haciendo un directo
think about it with your hands still eh with your
piénsalo con las manos quietas eh con
hands still
las manos
alanne you and I you and I like that
alanne tú y yo tú y yo así
think about it I put on my glasses if
piénsalo me pongo las gafas si es
necessary on telesalseo you sell out for
necesario en telesalseo te vendes por
20,000 and here for 10 bucks Javi the
20.000 y aquí por 10 pavos Javi el
crab is desperate but because
cangrejo está desesperado pero porque
you're full latan you're
ustedes sois full latan ustedes sois
full latan
full latan
inflation or so there I'll sell out for
inflación o seaa allí me vendo por
20,000 of course Alan Crespo has given away 10
20.000 claro Alan Crespo ha regalado 10
but what's happening What's happening What's happening I've been putting
pero qué pasa Qué pasa Qué pasa Yo llevo
up with you for like five or six years now the
como cinco o seis aguantándote ya el
feeling is already lost this is like
feeling ya se perdió esto es como las
butterflies right couples when they
mariposillas verdad las parejas cuando
start they have like butterflies in their
inician tienen como mariposillas en en
stomach no al and I already have
el estómago no al y yo ya tenemos
moths but closet moths
polillas pero polillas del armario en
like the ones that make holes you know in
plan de las que hacen agujero sabes en
clothes that's what we have  nillo I can't stand them
la ropa eso tenemos a nillo no las
let's see I'm getting lost here already
vamos a ver me estoy perdiendo aquí ya
Ivan you could do this perfectly
Iván tú podrías hacer perfectamente esto
and also with your little face it looked like with the
y además con la carita parecía con la
glasses and everything Ivan so don't worry don't
gafa y todo Iván así que no te rayes no
worry Ivan there's no danger there's no
te rayes Iván no hay peligro no hay
danger taking into account there's no
peligro teniendo en cuenta no hay
danger Ivan don't worry I
peligro Iván no te
already screwed up I'm sorry we have to
rayes ya la [__] Lo siento mismo
see it to see that everything is
tenemos que verlo para ver que esté todo
okay you know thanks for thinking outside the box no
bien sabes gracias por pensar en lata no
no but if not if you want I'll make you see
no pero si no es si quieres te hago ver
butterflies again Hey but that's
mariposa otra vez Oye pero eso es una
not a serious enough threat Ivan I think I
amenaza no bastante seria Iván creo que
could report you directly
te podría denunciar directamente
eh I think I could report you
eh creo que te podría denunciar
easily eh from here eh I'm
tranquilamente eh desde aquí eh se lo
telling Pablo But listen to me
digo a Pablo Pero ya escúchame
eh delox Don't tell me your technical life
eh delox No me cuentes tu vida técnica
you've already had time to upload the
habéis tenido tiempo ya para subir el
debate What's going on that you're not editing
debate Qué pasa que no estás editando
Titanic champion give me the [ __ ]
Titanic campeón que me des el [__]
debate that we
debate que
deserve eh Oh What a
merecemos eh Oh Qué
scare [ __ ] I [ __ ] I
susto cagado me he cagado se la he
ate it with potatoes I ate it with
comido con papas se la he comido con
potatoes I said Wow they're going to do tiktok
papas dije Wow esto te van a hacer tikt
this to you eh Be careful  Be careful
esto eh Ve con cuidado Ve con cuidado
everything is shaking because more than one person just
todo que que se a más de uno se le acaba
jumped off the keyboard like
de saltar el teclado de la mesa hecho
that more than one more than one would you like to
así más de uno más de uno te gustaría
bring Rubius no no yes I've read it No of
traer al Rubius no no si lo he leído No
course what kind of question is
claro es que Qué tipo de pregunta es
this no no I really want to bring
esta no no yo la verdad que traer a al
Rubius being the youtuber as well as from
Rubius siendo el youtuber así como de
Spain with the most impact he doesn't stop for
España con más impacto no para para para
what it's like prefo I prefer to bring
qué es en plan prefo prefiero traer a
manol 24 here from the chat to tell me what he
manol 24 aquí del chat que me cuente lo
did yesterday with his grandmother why do you
que hizo ayer con su abuela por qué te
think he invited me well he
piensas que me invitó a mí pues me
invited me because I'm like Man 24 from the
invitó a mí porque soy como Man 24 del
chat I understand that going around inviting Rubio I
chat entend que andar invitando al Rubio
only bring people who only bring people who are
solo traigo gente que solo traigo gente
broke if not no I don't invite him it's to
que esté funada si no no no lo invito
say if he says a no obviously I would
sea es decir si se mete un no obvio que
like I hope I hope the
me gustaría Ojalá ojalá se me de la
opportunity comes to me little by little I don't think it
oportunidad poco a poco igual no creo
's impossible he's not one of the profiles
que sea imposible no es de los perfiles
that I see as impossible in the end think that
que veo imposibles al final piensa que
Willy has to come yes yes yes no man
Willy tiene que venir si si si no hombre
Rubius is in Andorra I don't think it's
Rubio está en andorra tampoco creo que
impossible either me Rubius Rubius I don't think it's
sea imposible yo Rubius Rubius no creo
impossible how boring  El
que sea imposible qu aburrido El
Rubius It's that I don't either I consider that
Rubius Es que yo tampoco Considero que
El Rubius today is a
El Rubius a día de hoy sea el una
person with a great impact, I mean, he has
persona con gran impacto o sea él tiene
his community, he moves his community, he
su comunidad mueve su comunidad que
has his loyal community, you know, but not
tiene su comunidad fiel sabes pero no
like he's on everyone's lips
como que esté en Boca de todo el mundo
El Rubius all
El Rubius todo el
day maybe it's me eh, I don't
día a lo mejor soy yo eh que no me
know much, I know that this
entero de mucho sé que este fin de
weekend you'll watch the premiere of his series and
semana tú vele el estreno de su serie y
so on but it's not like he's always
demás pero como que no es como p todo el
in trends viral all the
tiempo en tendencias viral todo el
time people talk about
tiempo se habla de
him, he does
él
n't have his
no tiene su
[Music]
[Música]
community Hey, it's the first time that
comunidad Oye es la primera vez que
the melody played at night, no, it didn't
sonaba la melodía en la noche no no
change anything, a priori everything is coming
cambio nada que a priori viene todo
in December So we're
viene en diciembre Entonces estamos
talking about Rex Obviously ent because what I
hablando de de Rex Obvio ent porque lo
'm trying to do, we value it the
que estoy intentando que lo valoramos el
other day and it occurred to me is to square the
otro día y se me ocurrió es cuadrar el
Willy episode with the eslan when
episodio de Willy con los eslan cuando
the voting is
haya las votaciones
done Because obviously initially I didn't
clo Porque obvio yo inicialmente no
want to do any Shout but since
quería hacer ningún Shout pero ya que
now we see that there is strength to reach
ahora vemos que hay fuerza para llegar a
an eslan at least a nomination, I think I think I think
un eslan al menos a una nominación creo
a nomination I want to I think it
Creo creo que a una nominación quiero
makes sense to release
que creo que tiene sentido sacar el de
Willy's just when the
Willy justo cuando esté el formulario de
eslam form is out to enter  there the eh guys
los eslam para meter ahí el eh chicos
go to the form or whatever and let it be
vayan al formulario o sea y que que sea
my only colto action that I've done in my
mi único colto action que he hecho en mi
podcast history
historia del podcast
buff I wouldn't do that you in a
buf Yo no haría eso tú en un
[Music]
[Música]
podcast okay luar King I wouldn't do that
podcast vale luar Rey Yo no haría eso
You I don't know the truth promote yourself for
Tú no sé la verdad promocionarte para
the hlan taking advantage of a piece of
los hlan aprovechando un pedazo de
podcast
podcast
man I don't know the
tío No sé la
truth amlo says Javi it is said that delox
verdad amlo dice Javi se dice que delox
is in Argentina because they are
está en Argentina porque lo están
looking for him in Andorra because of the
buscando en andorra por lo de las
scams he is a
estafas está
fugitive source
fugitivo fuente
turboplane How old is anlo I'm not
turboplane Cuántos años tiene anlo no te
telling you this as a joke to the blocks but to
lo digo de cachondeo al blocks sino para
know more or less What is the audience
saber más o menos Cuál es la audiencia
that comes to believe something from that type
que llega a creerse algo de de ese tipo
of channels
de canales por
finally you would ask for members exactly of
fin tú pedirías miembros exactamente
course I bring Willy I ask for members in a
claro yo traigo a Willy pido miembros a
sack It's not that it's not that I don't publish the
saco No es que no es que no publico la
interview it's that I don't publish the
entrevista es que no publico la
interview until we get to what I
entrevista hasta que no lleguemos a qué
tell you
te digo
turb coherent my mother man my mother
yo turb coherente madre mía tío madre
well they are not deceiving me those of the
mía pues no me están funando las de las
blue tide the followers of Antonio AB
marea azul las seguidoras de Antonio AB
with one click that turboplane comes out
con un click que sale
something worth it with one click that
turboplane algo vale con un click que
comes out
sale
[Music]
[Música]
turboplane their personal data to Dallas
turboplane sus datos personales a Dallas
Yes yes you leak my personal data to
Sí sí le filtras Mis datos personales a
Dallas he's like a puppy But if you know
Dallas es como cachorro Pero si tú sabes
perfectly well what personal data if it
perfectamente qué datos personales si
was your [ __ ] phone number that you gave it
fue tu [__] teléfono que se lo diste tú
to three or four youtubers and they
a a tres o cuatro youtubers y se lo
gave it to Dallas at one point I
dieron al Dallas en un momento yo al
told Dallas no eh there I have the
Dallas le dije que no eh ahí tengo la
conversation Dallas asked me for my
conversación el Dallas me pidió el
phone number and I told him I'm going to ask his
teléfono y yo le dije le voy a pedir
permission to give it to you whenever they
permiso para dártelo yo siempre que me
ask me for a phone number I say
piden un teléfono digo
that I talked to the guy I talked to the guy
eso lo hablé con el chur Lo hablé con el
this I say is that I say guy you haven't noticed
chur esto digo es que digo chur tú no
when I don't remember why I
has caído cuando no me acuerdo por qué
talked to the
lo hablé con el
guy I say look at you the guy did
chur digo fíjate tú que el chur sí le
give the phone the guy the shur did
dio el teléfono el chur el shur sí le
give my phone number to Dallas without my permission one
dio mi teléfono al Dallas sin mi permiso
day Dallas has my phone number
en su día el Dallas tiene mi teléfono
because uncle shur gave it to him and he gave it to him
porque se lo dio el tío shur y se lo dio
without asking my permission that at the
sin pedirme el permiso que yo en su
time I say this guy What is he doing that he
momento digo yo este tío Qué hace que ha
gave my phone number but I'm not going to spend my
dado mi teléfono pero no me vo a poner
whole life saying that uncle sh gave
toda la vida a decir el tío sh ha dado
my personal data to
Mis datos personales a
Dallas What a character
Dallas Qué personaje
man because I've never asked for anything I haven't
tío porque nunca he pedido nada no he
asked for likes I haven't asked for it
pedido likes no he pedido que se
subscribe I haven't even said my name
suscriban no he dicho ni cómo me llamo
In fact there isn't a single episode that
De hecho no hay ni un solo episodio que
says my name it's a liar because I
diga mi nombre es mentiroso porque lo
did it in the text of the already and on Spotify
hice en el texto del ya y en Spotify
how do they know Listen to your podcast
cómo lo saben alguien Escucha tu podcast
on
en
Spotify yes
Spotify sí
Ah our esteemed animu we will deal with
Ah nuestra estimada animu trataremos
very interesting topics such as his very difficult
temas muy interesantes como su durísima
childhood and his unfavorable
infancia y su desfavorable situación
family situation his beginnings as a youtuber his
familiar sus comienzos como youtuber su
funa and that of Turbo has you all day long he
funa y el de Turbo te tiene todo el día
is still burning with flavor
en la boca está ardido aún
the lawsuit with delos he is going to
saburra la demanda con delos la va a
lose the lawsuit with delos it is a
perder la demanda con delos es es un
lawsuit of his career after supporting
demand de su carrera después de apoyar a
kcu his controversies cont the review
kcu sus polémicas cont la review
the things Take a seat and enjoy take
el cosas Toma asiento y disfruta toma
enjoy while a person
disfrutar mientras una persona
cries about Willy I do believe that Rubius is
llora de Willy yo s creo que Rubius es
a profile that can be valued
un perfil que se puede llegar a valorar
for 2024 in 2024 if I have planned
para 2024 en 2024 si tengo previsto
at least try to have the
cuanto menos tratar de que venga
same many profiles come the point is
igual muchos perfiles el punto está en
that I see that there are many podcasts for
que veo que hay muchos podcast por
example here in Argentina this
ejemplo aquí en Argentina está caja
black box you didn't tell me very Niche it's not like There are
negra no me dijiste muy Nicho no es como
very few people outside the country
que Hay muy poca gente fuera de el país
Main who really know that type of
Main que realmente conozca ese tipo de
content The only one who is  like
contenidos El único que está como
breaking down barriers a bit it's obviously a
rompiendo un poco barreras es obviamente
creative thing because you and Dalas
un creativo porque tú y Dalas se tienen
already have some trust but yeah I don't know what
ya cierta confianza pero si no sé a lo
you're referring to but I'm not going to cry let's
que te refieres pero que no voy a llorar
see I'm not going to cry either because
a ver que tampoco voy a llorar yo porque
someone gives my phone number to someone else
alguien le de mi teléfono a otro
I prefer that they don't give it to them I mean I
prefiero que no se lo den O sea yo yo
prefer that they don't give it to them or in fact
prefiero que no se lo den o sea de hecho
no I don't like it when they give it to them I mean yes I
no no me gusta que lo den O sea si yo
have a phone number but it's not a big
tengo un número de teléfono pero tampoco
deal either see what you're going to do
tampoco pasa nada ver tú qué te va se te
someone's going to hit you on the phone because
va a pegar alguien por el teléfono pues
if you don't want to talk to them they'll block it
si no les quieres hablar lo bloquean No
I don't know what else eh Because it's huge a
yo que sé qué más eh Porque es enorme un
Jordi Wild a Joe Rogan things like
Jordi Wild un Joe rogan sea cosas de
that break a lot there But there are
este estilo ahí rompen mucho Pero hay
others that are very much from the country so
otros que son como muy del país entonces
what I want is to bring people from all
lo que yo quiero es traer gente de todo
kinds of countries I would like to bring Dross
tipo de países me gustaría traer a Dross
I would like to bring people from the
me gustaría traer a personas del ámbito
public sphere Like for example and I say it Here it
público Como por ejemplo y lo digo Aquí
seems to me it would be epic a milei a mile I
me parece sería épico un milei un mile
would make it really hard then people from
me La pondría durísima entonces gente de
this my law right now no I don't see it
este mi ley ahora mismo no no lo veo yo
more accessible not for a
más accesible no para un podcast de
Delon podcast not being realistic not the same as
delon no siendo realistas no igual que
you  I say El Rubius Flow people who are
te digo El Rubius Flow gente que sea
like very well known in Latin America a Luisito
como muy reconocida en latam un Luisito
communicates things like this and and I would be very
comunica saa cosas de este estilo y y me
very excited politicians I
haría mucha mucha ilusión políticos me
would like to be able to bring singing is that they
gustaría poder traer cantando es que
are mentioning raret channels Yes but they are
están mencionando canales raret Sí pero
getting together with each other and they already
se están juntando entre ellos yván ya el
fall like the lowest of the lowest
caer como lo bajo de lo bajo de lo bajo
you know it's like falling from the lowest of the
sabes es como caer de lo bajo de lo bajo
lowest and I love it because I see it
de lo bajo y me encanta porque lo veo
from a distance I say
desde la distancia digo
wow How
wow Qué
sad before people in the entertainment industry
triste antes gente de la farándula hoy
today I brought
día traí
shocks if I read Instagram 90 because the
chocas si leyera Instagram 90 por lo el
point is that he literally doesn't read
punto está en que literal no lee
Instagram and the email that I sent him
Instagram y el correo que le envié no lo
I didn't read it and although I have a lot of
leí yo y aunque tengo un montón de
friends in common in fact [ __ ] I've
amigos en común de hecho [__] lo he
seen him in person you know at the party I
visto en persona sabes en la velada lo
saw him in person What happens is that anyway
vi en persona Lo que pasa que igualmente
I haven't interacted with him I've never
Yo no interactué con él Nunca he
interacted with him So I'm not going
interactuado con él Entonces tampoco voy
to take having it there the one who said
a [__] tenerlo ahí el que ha dicho
Now
Ahora
and And although I have a lot of friends in
y Y aunque tengo un montón de amigos en
common in fact [ __ ] I've seen him in
común de hecho [__] lo he visto en
person and 30% what the point is that he
persona y 30% lo que el el punto está en
literally doesn't read Instagram and the email
que literal no lee Instagram y el correo
that I sent him I didn't  I read And although I have
que le envié no lo leyo Y aunque tengo
a lot of friends in common in fact
un montón de amigos en común de hecho
[ __ ] I've seen him in person you know at the
[__] lo he visto en persona sabes en la
party I saw him in person What happens is that
velada lo vi en persona Lo que pasa que
I still didn't interact with him I've never
igualmente Yo no interactué con él Nunca
interacted with him delox went to the
he interactuado con él delox fue a la
party delox went to the party So I'm
velada delox fue a la velada Entonces
not going to take it having him there to to
tampoco voy a [__] tenerlo ahí a a a
two 2 Met and say hello hello want to
dos 2 Met y decirle hola hola quier
come my podcast you know it's not a
venir mi podcast no sabes tampoco es
plan either but I had people that
plan pero yo tenía personas que me
made me really excited like obviously
hacían mucha ilusión como era obviamente
Willy Rex is a very good friend of mine he is a
Willy Rex es muy buen amigo mío es una
person that I think can give an
persona que creo que puede dar un
extraordinary podcast because
podcast extraordinario el millo porque
I really like what he does the content
me Mola mucho lo que hace el contenido
that he's been doing for a long time I
que lleva haciendo mucho tiempo me Mola
really like the character that he has on social networks zeros
mucho el personaje que tiene en redes
sper that I've already recorded it
ceros sper que ya lo he grabado tema
debate topic When does it come out everyone is going to
debate Cuándo sale que todos se van a
ask each other and we say there's no date and
preguntar y decimos no hay una fecha y
no one is going to see it I don't have the balls
ni la va a ver no me sale los [__]
to give a date because it gives me an
dar una fecha porque me da un ataque de
anxiety attack Okay then it will come it will
ansiedad Vale entonces ya vendrá ya
come when it has to come The idea is for it to
vendrá cuando tenga que venir La idea es
come out this month or Yes okay the idea is it's a
que salga este mes o Sí vale la idea es
September project which was de
es proyecto de septiembre que era el
nimu's podcast and then the debate
podcast de de nimu más luego el debate
so this September in the worst
entonces este septiembre en El peor de
case scenario you have 16 days left not that it will
los casos os quedan 16 días no que
have 30 days this month I don't know how many it has
tendrá 30 días este mes no sé cuántos
but around there Go on you have left you have
tiene pero por ahí Andá os quedan os
around
quedan alrededor de
two so it supports cocu weeks more or
dos o sea que apoya cocu semanas más o
less 30 Okay so about two weeks in
menos 30 Vale pues unas dos semanas en
those two weeks in some day
esas dos semanas en algún día debería de
the podcast should come out
salir el podcast
So it doesn't happen that much or delox
Entonces tampoco pasa tanto o delox nos
has us I would like delox to interview
ha Yo quisiera que delox entreviste a
bukele bukele would lend himself a lot to this
bukele bukele se prestaría mucho este
type of things eh What happens is that I don't
tipo de cosas eh Lo que pasa es que no
think no I don't
creo
think he's accessible I don't see him as
no no creo que sea accesible no lo veo
very much the profile that would lend himself to this
muy del perfil que se prestaría este
type of things let's see the
tipo de cosas a ver los políticos
Spanish politicians they take their walk eh
españoles se se hacen su su paseito eh
through all the channels eh I could have
por todos los canales eh yo pude haber
interviewed let's
entrevistado
see I Well I could have
al a ver yo Yo bueno yo pude haber
interviewed one okay I'm not going to say
entrevistado a uno vale no voy a decir a
who but I didn't have time I didn't
quién pero no me no me dio tiempo no me
have time to prepare it well or to
daba tiempo a prepará mela bien ni a
study it well the subject is not my it's not
estudiarme bien el tema no es mi no es
my subject If I would have liked to
mi temática Si me hubiera gustado
do it the truth but of course It's that to
hacerla la verdad pero claro Es que para
do it I would like to do it for
hacerla me gustaría hacerla a
everyone good melon J Sas good melon jar
todos buen melón J Sas buen melón jar
good melon you just
buen melón acabas de
opened
abrir
we could we all go to
podríamos podríamos irnos todos para
kiik and now I donate all 200
kiik y que me doné ahora todos los 200
members but let's
miembros pero a
see It's that I,
k a ver Es que yo
I, if I interview one I would
me yo si si entrevisto a uno yo me
like to interview all
gustaría entrevistar a los
four the four that are present if
cuatro a los cuatro que se presentan si
I'm going to interview one I would like to
yo voy a entrevistar a uno me gustaría
interview all four but
entrevistar a los cuatro pero
interview only one No because
entrevistar a uno solo No porque
then your channel is like
entonces como que tu canal es una
another political campaign for that party You
campaña política más de ese partido
know if I interview one like
Sabes Yo si entrevisto a uno comoo hace
El Hormiguero does that the four El
El Hormiguero que pasen los cuatro El
Hormiguero Ana Rosa play all the programs
Hormiguero Ana Rosa todos los programas
well in conditions pum come on more
bien en condiciones pum venga más
members joma jomoro family Let's see I
miembros joma jomoro familia A ver os
have to tell you one thing Before you hit
tengo que decir una cosa Antes de darle
Play jomar oro is crying because you
al Play jomar oro está llorando porque
gave me more
me habéis regalado más
members all night asking says
miembros toda la noche pidiendo dice
Mariano let's see what we do to this type of
Mariano a ver qué le hacemos a este tipo
people kids what would
de personas chavales qué le contestaría
you answer Mariano is super offended
ustedes Mariano está super ofendido
jomar oro
jomar oro
too What would you do what would you do to
también Qué le haríais qué le haríais a
this type of person what would you
este tipo de persona qué le
tell him give away more No man no no no no no no no no no no no no let's
diríais regalen más No hombre no no no
see
no no no no no no no no no no a ver
how much we
cuánt
go
vamos
184 what a [ __ ] shame eh What a [ __ ]
184 qué [__] vergüenza eh Qué [__]
shame 184 members being here 2000
vergüenza 184 miembros estando aquí 2000
people
personas
man I would give it B no don't give it B don't give it
tío yo le daría B no no le de B no le de
B do the
B hacer los
Mods several things first that it is not
Mods varias cosas primero que no es
capable need a spoiler near the
capaz necesar un spoiler cerca del
teaser and second that it loves that they read
teaser y segundo que le encanta que leen
everywhere yarr the
por todos lados yarr el
wool Oh God stop cringe at least here there are no
lano Ay Dios alto cringe al menos aquí
people looking at us on the street with a
no hay gente mirándonos por la calle con
face of what the [ __ ] is this that is
cara de qué [__] es esto que está
happening that it will give you an
pasando que te va a dar un ataque
epileptic attack Give me the
epiléptico Ponme la
part you and me alne
parte tú y yo alne
think about it Remember humility Javi Yes yes yes
piénsalo Recuerda la humildad Javi Sí sí
humility humility do not give away
sí la humildad la humildad no regalis
more members worth what is left of the
más miembros vale lo que queda de
night do not give away more members is what is
noche no regalis más miembros es lo que
left of the night okay
queda de noche vale
alanne you me like that think about it a
alanne tu yo así piénsalo un
direct queel dan idiot is the one queel
directito queel dan boludo es el queel
Dan
Dan
who came out to
quién saló al
Anne
Anne
Oh How
Oh Qué
cute, delox looks very happy
lindos se le ve muy feliz al delox
listen to me I have another exact one I
escúchame tengo otro exato
have another excerpt and it is a fight
más tengo otro extracto y es una pelea
between two influencers who were a couple
entre dos influencer que eran pareja
You have another excerpt here that
Tú tengo otro extracto aquí que me ha
luare put me another  excerpt has put me
puesto luare otro estracto me ha puesto
uncle He keeps sending me work
tío No para de mandarme trabajo
luare
luare
noada tomorrow luares this Leave it for
noada mañana luares este Déjalo para
tomorrow this put it for tomorrow I have to
mañana este ponlo para mañana que tengo
record the news man otherwise I won't
que grabar el noticiero tío que si no no
record it I have to record the news
lo grabo tengo que grabar el noticiero
both of kids As of
tanto de chavalería Como de
gentlemen that record the
señoreros que grabar el
news guys guys
noti chicos
a huge kiss okay I'm going to
chicos un beso enorme vale me voy a
record the news because otherwise it won't record
grabar el noti es que si no no se graba
I'm going to record the news
voy a grabar el noti
eh go to the main channel to the
eh iros para el canal principal al
last video ok meanwhile if you want
último vídeo vale de mientras si queréis
more gossip go to the main channel jav
más salseo iros al Canal principal jav
oliveira to the last video that I uploaded
oliveira al último vídeo que he subido
okay And in the next few hours the next one will be out
vale Y en las próximas horas estará el
a huge kiss I love you all
siguiente un beso enorme os quiero
so much bye bye okay bye bye bye a
muchísimo chao chao vale chao
kiss a kiss family
chao chao chao un beso un beso familia
We love you all so much
Se os quiere muchísimo
[Music]
[Música]
and
y